坦 克 大 决 战
主演：亨利・方达
罗伯特・肖
罗伯特・雷恩
达那・安德鲁斯
导演：肯・安纳金
1944年12月
December, 1944.
美军与英军正迈向 他们胜利之路
British and American armies were on the threshold of victory.
越过了半个欧洲 盟军终于对德国本土
Stretched across half of Europe, the Allies gathered themselves...
形成了合围
... for the final assault on Germany.
在北方有蒙哥马利的第八军
To the north stood Montgomery's Eighth Army...
在南方有巴顿的第三军
... to the south, Patton's Third.
在中央，沿着88哩长的前线
In the center, along an 88-mile front...
几个久经征战而疲乏的美军师 在那个区域安静的休养着
... a few battle-weary American divisions rested in a quiet sector.
对他们而言 战争似乎已经赢了
To them, the war seemed already won.
这就是他们的故事
This is their story.
中校 我们在这森林飞了一星期
We've been flying over these woods all week.
除了树以外什么也没有 我们回去吧！
There's nothing but trees. Let's turn back.
- 饿了吗？ 乔  - 战争已经结束了
- Getting hungry, Joe?  - The war is over.
我听说后勤司令部要下令 送我们回国去过圣诞节
I hear GHQ is cutting orders to ship us home for Christmas.
乔，德国还有六百万武装部队
The German army still has 6 million men carrying arms.
我没听说他们要去过圣诞节
I haven't heard they're going home for Christmas.
在那了
Hey, there it is...
德国陆军！
...the German army.
我们飞下去看看！
Let's go down and have a look.
- 再飞一次！乔，我要拍照  - 好
- Buzz him again. I wanna get a picture.  - Okay.
这一次让你的马达 发点声音出来 让他往上看！
This time, gun your engine. Make him look up.
生效了
It worked.
再飞一次，我要再拍一张
Swing around. I wanna get another one.
康拉德
Conrad.
我以你为耻
I am ashamed of you.
站起来
Get up.
我们可能会死的，长官
They could have killed us, sir.
你若仔细的看清楚那飞机
If you'd taken the pains to have looked carefully...
你会发现是 没有武装的侦察机！
...you would have observed it was an unarmed reconnaissance plane.
他会留在空中叫 战斗机来射我们
You would stay in the car if it were a fighter plane shooting at us.
我还没打输 也不想死在车后座
I did not lose a war to die in the back seat of a car.
上校认为我们有选择的权利？ 选我们死在那里？
Does the colonel think any of us has a choice where we will die?
我想你是死在家里的床上 康拉德
I know where you'll die, Conrad, at home, in your own bed.
所以上校计划要换掉我
Is the colonel trying to get rid of me?
我认为世界预备好 要弄掉我们俩
I think that the world is going to get rid of both of us.
把你的帽子捡起来 把它戴上
Pick up your cap! Put it on.
试着看起来像个军人
Try to look like a soldier!
当个军人又有什么好的？
What good is a soldier anyhow?
你胜了，你在这与这个为伍
He wins, he loses.
看看我现在又是什么样子
What's he good for anyhow?
康拉德！ 我以前告诉过你，
Conrad, I've told you before...
别让引擎空转 汽油就如同血液一样宝贵！
...never leave the motor running. Petrol is blood.
抱歉，长官，
I'm sorry, sir.
不会再发生了
It won't happen again.
看来十点钟方向的地面上 有东西 我们去看看
Looks like something on the ground at 10 o'clock. Let's take a look.
什么也没有
Nothing.
我们回去吧！
Let's go home.
海斯勒上校到了
Herr Oberst Hessler is here.
是！是！海斯勒上校
这边走，长官
- 海斯勒上校，长官  - 好的
- Colonel Hessler, sir.  - Yes.
海斯勒！
Well, Hessler.
好久不见了
It has been a long time.
再见到你太好了
How good it is to see you again.
你神采依旧
You look the same.
有点…
Little...
也许有点瘦了
Little leaner perhaps.
你的苏俄前线 并没让我好好发挥 将军
The Russian front does not put meat on a man's bones, general.
是的 战争影响了我们每一个人
Ah, yes. War is hard on all of us.
- 中央暖气系统  - 是啊
- Central heating.  - Yeah.
水晶吊灯
Crystal chandeliers.
你这间房间真是舒适
You have a nice cellar.
戈林元帅给了我那幅画
Field Marshal Goring gave me that painting.
很可爱，不是吗？
Lovely, isn't it?
想想是他去年在巴黎 找到的交易
I imagine he found a bargain in Paris last year.
我的伍长在外面 开车开的很累
My corporal's waiting. He's had a hard drive.
你想在这些废墟的某处 能找张床
Do you suppose there's somewhere in these ruins he can find a bed?
坐，海斯勒
Sit down, Hessler.
你得对德国人民的天才 有点信心
You have too little faith in the genius of the German people.
几块石头被打倒了
A few stones have been knocked down...
但我们的国家依然坚强 比以前更团结，更有生机
...but our country's strong, united, determined...
更有生产效率
...and more productive than ever.
盟国以为他们对我们持续轰炸能够打击我们的士气
The Allies think that their constant air raids have undermined our morale.
- 这永远不会发生的  - 你为何找我来此？ 将军
- This they'll never do.  - Why have you sent for me, general?
你是我们最佳的战车指挥官 海斯勒
You are our finest panzer commander, Hessler.
能带我们走向胜利的人
You will lead us to victory.
我们德国现在像冰山一样
Our Germany is now like an iceberg.
只有小部份能在表面看到
Only a fraction of it can be seen on the surface.
让我带你看看一些成果
Let me show you some of the results...
德国在地下所制造的
...of what Germany has produced underground.
这是新的德国
You will discover a new Germany...
而当个德国人会有新的骄傲
...and will take a new pride in being a German.
我们最新的飞机
Our latest airplane.
喷射机
A jet.
时速高达九百公里
It flies at more than 900 kilometers per hour.
六个月之内 我们就能造足够的喷射机
Within six months, we will have enough jet fighters...
把盟军空中的 每架飞机都打下来
...to shoot down every Allied plane in the air.
我们的V1火箭摧毁了20%的伦敦
Our V-1 rocket destroyed 20 percent of London.
V2会彻底的毁掉那城市
The V-2 will utterly smash the city.
我们新型的70吨的虎型坦克
The new 70-ton King Tiger tank.
较美军坦克的火力大两倍半
It has two-and-a-half times the firepower...
装甲要厚两倍！
...and double the armor of the American tanks.
我们德国离结束还早呢！ 不是吗？
Our Germany is far from finished, Hessler.
很漂亮的模型，将军
It's a very beautiful model, general.
那证明了我们的元首 是最佳的玩具制造者
It proves that the Germans are still the world's best toy makers.
我们今日所做的玩具 不是小孩的
The toys we are making these days are not for children.
让我带你去看它们
Let me show them to you.
举起手
Hands up! Get on over.
靠墙站，举起手
Hold it! Put them up! Stand against the wall. Put them up, general.
孩子们
Well, boys...
好像我们抓到一些大鱼
...looks like we've caught ourselves a couple of big fish.
- 一条肥鱼  - 够了
- One nice, fat Kraut trout.  - That's enough, now.
对不起，将军我们正在搞突击演习
Sorry, general. We are just rehearsing a commando raid.
很好
Very good.
不错吧，是不是？
Not bad, Hessler, huh?
他们把你蒙骗了？
Had you fooled, didn't they?
完全
Completely.
不幸的是，我很能玩游戏
Unfortunately, I am beyond playing games.
不是游戏
Oh, this is no game.
是德国士兵，全都是
These are German soldiers, all of them.
训练有素的德国士兵
Trained German soldiers.
迪波命令手榴弹兵紧跟坦克1旅
Diepel commands the panzer grenadiers attached to the 1 st Tank Brigade.
这些人会与他们一同作战
These men will work with him.
迪波少校，请向上校解释
Major Diepel, kindly explain Operation Transit to the colonel.
士兵会在美国线后面伞降
The soldiers will be parachuted behind the American lines.
他们的任务是破坏敌军通讯
Their mission: To disrupt enemy communications.
我们组织了许多此类的队伍
We have organized many such teams.
每支队伍由一名在美国居住过的人领导
Each will be led by a man who has actually lived in America.
舒马赫在德州居住了12年
Schumacher here lived in Texas for 12 years...
然后才回到祖国
...before returning to the fatherland.
告诉我，中尉，你最喜欢的棒球选手是谁？
Tell me, lieutenant, who is your favorite baseball player?
- 鲁・格里克  - 因为他打出了最多的本垒打？
- Lou Gehrig.  - Because he's hit the most home runs?
不，是贝比・鲁斯，在1927年打出60个本垒打
No, sir. Babe Ruth hit the most home runs, 60 in 1927.
你对希特勒有何看法？
And what's your opinion of Adolf Hitler?
作为一名美国人我对这人比较反感
As an American, my opinion would be offensive to these gentlemen.
众位，作为一名美国军官你不与德国人一样看待
Come, lieutenant. As an American officer, you care nothing for German opinion.
希特勒是一个狂热的奥地利粉漆工
Adolf Hitler is a crazy, Austrian housepainter.
他是个疯子，以为比全世界的人都有智慧
He's a madman who thinks he knows more than the whole general's staff.
他使德国走向彻底毁灭
And he's leading Germany to complete, total destruction.
你可能言之有过了
Perhaps you are going too far.
不要假装了，他们的内心都是美国人的想法
To carry off this great deception, even their reflexes must be American.
你的想法很值得恭喜，中尉
Your reflexes are to be congratulated, lieutenant.
无礼的人
Insolent man.
让他开心一下
Let him have his fun now.
若他被俘他会被当作间谍杀死
If he is captured, he will be shot as a spy.
若他幸存他会被当作叛徒杀死
And if he survives, he can be shot as a traitor.
你得承认我们检查很严密
You must admit, we are very thorough.
即使有通行证也无法到此
Even a pass won't get you through here.
我们要攻击 并通过罗森关口
We will attack through the Losheim Gap.
那里只有一个营的兵力防守
It's defended only by a single battalion.
在施奈亚芙的美军师会被切断
The American division on the Schnee Eifel will be cut off.
那么瓦尔河的桥会在我们手中
Then the Our River Bridge will be in our hands.
由那里到安不列芙是喉头地带
From there, on to Ambleve, with its road network.
四天之后，我们会越过马士河
In four days, we will be across the River Meuse.
目标是在那里呢？
The strategic objective?
安特卫普
Antwerp.
我们攻下了安特卫普 会将敌军兵力分割为二
By taking Antwerp, we split the enemy forces in two.
他们要花18个月才能恢复
It will take them 18 months to recover.
到那时候我们的喷射机 就能占有空中优势
By then, we will have air superiority with our jet engines.
甚至我们更有独特的武器
And we will have even more significant weapons.
一种能在一瞬间 毁灭整城的武器
Weapons which can destroy an entire city with a single blast.
你遗忘了一个重要的细节 将军
You have forgotten one important detail, general.
盟军现有的空中优势
With their present control of the air, the Allies will smash our tanks...
会夷平我们的坦克、机枪部队
...machine-gun our troops, bomb the bridges...
炸掉桥及切断我们的通信
...and cut our communications.
假使我告诉你 不会有盟军飞机呢
Suppose I tell you there will be no Allied planes.
另一种秘密武器
Another secret weapon?
来自挪威的史必兹堡
From Spitzbergen, Norway...
世界最北端的气象站
...the northernmost weather station in the world.
我等这份报告已经两个月了
We have been waiting two months for this report.
低气压自12月16日起南下
"A low-pressure area over northern Europe, starting December 16th.
云雾皆浓，任何飞机不能起飞
Low clouds and fog which will ground all aircraft."
- 有多久？  - 够久了
- How long?  - Long enough...
若我们能和 我们定的时间表同速
...if we keep strictly to our timetable.
不寻常的钟，不是吗？
Unusual clock, isn't it?
只有一圈
It has only one cycle.
50个小时
Fifty hours.
我们有足够的资源 供50个小时的全力攻击
We have the resources for 50 hours, full-scale attack.
地图，时钟，玩具
Maps, clocks, toys.
但我要用什么来作战呢？
But with what will I fight?
海斯勒上校
Colonel Hessler...
我要任命你 当我们机械化前锋的指挥官
...l'm putting you in command of our armored spearhead.
可以
It can be done.
（师部）
只是来聊天的
This came in from SHAEF.
我今天收到家里寄的圣诞蛋糕
I got a Christmas cake from home today.
- 我想我还会在这里吃它  - 立刻把这个发出去
- Think I'll still be here to eat it?  - Send this right through.
立刻冲洗这个 一经到定影液后 就立刻拿来给我
Develop this. Bring me the prints as soon as they come out.
- 是的，长官  - 哈，凯利
- Yes, sir.  - Hello, Kiley.
在你今早的搜索中 找到德军了吗？
Find any Germans under your bed this morning?
也许明晚一晚都在那行军 我一刻也睡不着
Marching around under there all night. Couldn't sleep a wink.
是命令！
That's an order.
我要那菜单上的每一样东西 送到师里每位弟兄的手中
I want every item on that menu delivered to every soldier in the division...
尤其是那些在前线的
...especially those in the forward positions.
我要它们及时送到 以便当做圣诞晚餐
And I want them delivered in time for Christmas dinner.
我们的情报部队 自敌人间谍那里得到的
Counterintelligence picked this up from an enemy agent.
日期是11月29日
Dated November 29th.
由元帅凯特尔发出，最高机密
"From Field Marshal Keitel. Most secret.
会说英文的军官与士兵 因特别任务召集
Officers and men who speak English are wanted for special mission.
志愿者向科勒将军的总部报到
Volunteers will report to General Kohler's headquarters."
- 你有何想法？  - 我个人的意见是，将军
- What do you make of it?  - You know my opinion.
只是另一次的确认 他们要攻击我们了
This is one more confirmation. They're going to attack.
得了吧！凯利！ 别又来那一套了
Oh, come on, Kiley, not that again.
他们可能预备将第五纵队 空投在我们的阵线后面
They're probably preparing a fifth column to drop behind our lines.
你也在国务院待过吗？ 凯利
Were you in the State Department too, Kiley?
我以为你的经验局限在 警务工作
I thought your experience was limited to police work.
我当刑警并不使我 失去思考资格
Having been an inspector of police doesn't disqualify me from thinking.
所有的警察都思想熟虑
All cops aren't flatfoots.
你有限的军事经验
Your limited military experience...
使我们对你的结论没什么信心 若你认为…
...doesn't inspire confidence in your conclusions. If you think...
为何你一直说他们预备攻击
Why do you keep saying they're mounting an offensive?
我在战前花了20年 都在问问题
I spent 20 years before the war asking questions.
而自登陆欧洲后 你又叫我做同样的事情
Ever since D-day, you've had me doing the same thing...
侦讯战俘
...interrogating prisoners.
我只能报告我所知道的
I can only report what I've learned.
面对我们的德军士兵 仍然是一个没有击溃的敌军
The German soldier facing us is still an undefeated enemy.
他们仍然能作战！ 他们的领袖知道那一点！
He can still fight. His leaders know that.
只要他们还能作战 他们就会攻击
As long as he can fight, they'll attack.
我的科里还有其他十位军官
I have 10 other officers in my section.
我们看到的是同样的资料 看到与你相同的事实，凯利
We see the same information, get the same facts as you, Kiley.
所有的人都得到同样的答案 而你出来的是完全相反的
All of us come up with one answer, you come up with the complete opposite.
当十个人都说你醉了 你最好躺下来！
When 10 men tell you you're drunk, you'd better lie down.
比瑞奇上校 你也许是我的上司
Colonel Pritchard, you may be my superior officer...
他是的
He is.
打扰，长官 这是你要的照片，中校
Excuse me. Here are the prints you wanted.
谢谢
Thank you.
看看这上面的是什么
Look what showed up on this one.
看看阿登森林
I took it over the Ardennes.
这是辆虎型坦克，或不是？
Is this a Tiger tank, or isn't it?
这上面的是它
So it appears.
但一只老虎不能构成整座森林 长官
One tiger doesn't make a jungle, sir.
我期待在森林中看到老虎 但我在宁静的邻近地区 看到一只
I expect tigers in jungles. When I discover one in a peaceful neighborhood...
我建议我们大家都看看床底下
...I recommend all of us take a good look under our beds.
打扰了，长官
Excuse me, sir.
到外面去
Step outside.
请你允许，长官
With your permission, sir.
这是总部来的，凯利 最高机密
This is from headquarters, Kiley. Top-secret.
第三军奉令攻击德国萨尔区
The Third Army has been ordered to attack the Germans in the Saar.
巴顿将军已进攻了两天了
General Patton is launching the offensive in two days.
总部会命令整个军进攻南方
Does it seem possible...
而在北方敌人 会攻击阿登地区
...headquarters would commit an entire army to an offensive in the south...
这对你是否没有一点道理？
...if there were any possibility of the Germans attacking in the Ardennes?
我们全都尊敬总部 但他们可能会出错的
With all due respect to headquarters, they could be wrong.
总之还是把这个送去总部
Send this to headquarters anyway.
比瑞奇 那坦克上似乎有新配备
There seem to be new features on that tank.
- 是的，长官  - 还有别的事吗？
- Yes, sir.  - Anything else?
我想查查这位德国军官
Yes, sir. I'd like a rundown on this German officer.
- 好的，把这一起送去  - 是的，长官
- All right, send this along.  - Yes, sir.
你最好到前线 去叫他们捉新战俘
Get up to the line and tell them to grab some new prisoners.
- 我对我能得到的任何新资料都感兴趣  - 是的，长官
- I'm interested in any fresh information.  - Yes, sir.
还有一件事 你在侦察机里做什么？
One thing more. What are you doing in a reconnaissance plane?
我们不是请你来当战斗军人的
We're not paying you to be a combat soldier.
- 想要一个人缩短这场战争？  - 不是，长官
- Trying to shorten the war by yourself?  - No, sir.
只是想确定能如愿的安享你订的那份圣诞晚餐
Just wanna make sure I can enjoy that nice Christmas dinner you ordered.
我看到上校又有食欲了
I see the colonel's in fine appetite again.
我是的
I am.
陪我喝杯酒吧！
Join me in a glass of wine.
谢谢你，长官
Thank you, sir.
- 坐下  - 谢谢
- Sit down.  - Thanks.
康拉德
Conrad.
说话呀
Speak.
上校希望我说些什么呢？
What does the colonel wish me to say?
说你心里的话，说真话
Speak your mind, the truth.
别怕，康拉德 总得有人对我说真话
Don't be afraid, Conrad. I must have someone to tell me the truth.
我很幸运能服侍一位聪明的人
I've always been fortunate to serve under brilliant men...
他知道所有的事
...who know everything.
由那全部，我知道一件事
From them, I've learned one thing:
当一切都失去时 但这位聪明人并未失去希望
When all was lost, these brilliant men never lost hope.
我仰慕那一点
I admire that.
你对这个人还仰慕那些呢？
What else do you admire about these men?
幻像
The illusion.
也许我没用对字，上校
Maybe I'm not using the right word, colonel.
我不是个受过教育的人
I'm not an educated man.
希望永远都还有一次机会
The hope that there is always one more chance.
那是，你知道吗？ 幻像
That is the illusion.
继续，康拉德，说的非常好
Go on, Conrad. Yes, that's very good.
这不是我说这种事的地方
It's not my place to speak of such things.
说呀！
Go on.
我命令你说
I order you to.
上校
Colonel...
这个新指挥权 是幻像
...this new command is an illusion.
放弃吧！
Give it up.
我是马丁海斯勒
I am Martin Hessler.
四年前我的坦克在一周之内
Four years ago, my panzers overran Poland in one week.
征服了波兰，那不是幻像
That was no illusion.
39天我的坦克一路打到巴黎 那不是幻像
In 39 days, my tanks smashed all the way to Paris. That was no illusion.
我征服了克里米亚 那不是幻像
I conquered the Crimea. That was no illusion.
今天
Today...
给了我一个旅的虎型坦克
...I was given a brigade of Tiger tanks.
当我有一旅的坦克
When I have a brigade of tanks...
那就是现实
...that is reality.
但谁是驾驶那些坦克的人
And who will drive your tanks?
你率领的人是军人
The men you led were soldiers. Veteran soldiers.
还有剩下的吗？
Are there any left?
他们现在给你的是什么？
What will they give you now?
我在波兰，法国，克里米亚 都与你并肩在一起
I was by your side in Poland, France, Crimea.
看看我，上校 我不是那个人了
Look at me, colonel, I'm not the same man.
我今天被一架 没有武装的侦察机吓的半死！
I jumped in a ditch today at the sight of an unarmed reconnaissance plane.
我的两个儿子 记得我是勇敢战士
My two boys remember me as a good soldier.
他们不会相信的
They wouldn't believe it.
但是上校，我不是唯一的一个
But, colonel, I am not the only one.
你能多确定你的人 会与坦克共存亡？
How sure can you be of the men who will drive your tanks?
- 基伯少校  - 稍待！上校
- Major Diepel?  - [Speak German]
- 基伯  - 有
- Diepel.  - Yep.
- 我要见我的坦克连长 立刻召集  - 他们马上来
- I want to see my tank commanders. Have them assembled at once.  - - [Speak German]
- 康拉德 我的靴子  - 有
- Conrad, my boots.  - Yep.
立正！
你的战车连长！长官
Your commanders, sir.
孩子！太多孩子了
Boys. Too many boys.
第一场战役会把他们变成男人
The first battle will turn them into men.
昔日我们生活六个月才上战场
In the old days, I lived six months with my men...
我认得他们，他们认得我 而这些是陌生人
...before going into action. I knew them, they knew me. These are strangers.
太多孩子了
Too many boys.
他们从来没被击败过
They have never tasted defeat.
他们知道什么在等着他们吗？
Do they know what is expected of them?
他们预备好为你而死！
They are ready to die for you.
你能要求更多吗？
Can you ask more?
唱！
Sing.
大声点！
Louder.
慢点！慢点
Hold it. Hold it.
前进 有军官在这，
Pull up. We got brass on our tail. Take it...
往前开！白痴
Pull it forward, you idiot!
去死吧！ 往前进！白痴
Drop dead. Pull it forward, you idiot!
只要一点点，慢一点
Just a little bit. Hold it.
停！停！
Hold it! Hold it!
你把我的货物弄掉下来了
You're dropping my merchandise!
快点，艾迪！快点出来
Barrel and Eddie, come on out of there.
快点！高林
Come on, Cortland.
大灾难！
Disaster.
没破 好一个驾驶 没打破算你运气好
Solid. Some driver, huh? Lucky thing for you nothing's busted.
- 向我的工会投诉吧！  - 是，去吧，把它们绑好
- Complain to my union.  - Yeah, go ahead, tie it up.
- 我们接近敌区了吗？  - 太近了
- We near enemy territory yet?  - Too near.
- 杜丹，给我根烟  - 我不抽烟
- Give me a cigarette.  - I don't smoke.
上士 我们何时才能看到德国人
Sarge, when will we see some Germans?
- 你呢？ 贝罗  - 抽你自己的吧
- Barrel?  - Smoke your own.
你有烟吗？ 艾迪
Got a cigarette, Eddie?
- 你开玩笑  - 一些便宜货
- You kidding?  - You cheapskates.
由我的袋子里拿条烟给我
Reach into my bag, get me a carton of cigarettes.
你和德国人有那不对劲？
What's with you and the Germans?
没什么，我只没看过而已
Nothing. I just ain't never seen one.
你知道 我甚至没见过德国飞机
You know, I've never even seen a German plane.
上士，我们何时能打仗？
Sarge, when are we gonna get in the action?
你是疯子吗？
What are you, some kind of a nut?
他们派给我们的 是那种补充兵？
What kind of replacements they sending us, huh?
我想看打仗
"I wanna see action."
- 这是什么？  - 把它放回去，那是货物
- What's this?  - Put that back. That's merchandise.
别告诉我 我们去的地方有女人
Don't tell me there's women where we're going.
- 你要把这个送给谁？  - 葛菲不会送东西给人
- Who are you gonna give these to?  - Guffy don't give nothing.
- 他靠它们挣钱  - 你继续绑你的
- He's peddling them.  - You keep tying it up.
- 卖它们？ 卖给谁？  - 前线的人
- Peddling them? To who?  - The boys in the front.
到了德国就需要它了 那里有很多妞！
They're gonna need that in Germany. There's lots of broads there.
- 法国香水  - 香槟
- French perfume.  - Champagne.
在我们去的地方一瓶值30元
That's gonna bring me 30 bills a bottle where we're going.
因为对我们的人来说 没有任何东西是太好了
Because there's nothing, nothing too good for our boys.
- 这里面是什么？  - 那是邮件
- Yeah. What's in here?  - That's the mail.
你连那个也要收费吗？
Are you gonna charge them something for that too?
- 有何不可？他们不会拒绝的  - 只是开玩笑，上士 只是开玩笑
- No, they wouldn't sit still for that.  - Just kidding, sarge. Just kidding.
不，当你有这种好点子时 不管是什么我都要你告诉我
No. When you get these thoughts, tell me anyway...
因为我不要再回家当穷光蛋
...because one thing I'm not going back home again is poor.
继续想，小鬼，很好
Keep thinking, kid. Very nice.
德军？
Germans?
这是最前线了
This is the up-front front.
真是群清醒的孩子们
Wide awake bunch of boys.
- 你们不该派卫兵站岗吗？  - 抱歉，长官 我才进去一会儿
- Don't you people ever post a sentry?  - I'm sorry, sir. I came in for a second.
玩什么花样？ 关门！
What's the matter? Close the pneumonia hole.
- 你在那生的？ 谷仓吗？  - 抱歉，长官，
- What were you born in, a barn?  - Oh, sorry, sir.
我们不知道是你
We didn't know it was you.
- 乌兰斯基少校呢？  - 他在那边，长官
- Major Wolenski?  - He's over there, sir.
中校，我没料到有高阶军官来 否则我会叫我的人精明点
Hello, colonel. I wasn't expecting a visit or I'd have had my men smarten up.
你好 给中校来点热咖啡
How are you? Hot coffee for the colonel.
到这边来暖和一下
Come over and get warm.
你这蛮轻松的
You run a pretty loose outfit here.
那收音机一直在叫着 圣诞节时我们全都回家去了
That radio's been yakking between Christmas carols we're all going home.
请坐
Here, sit down.
想要在这种只想保暖的地方
It's tough keeping discipline when the only action...
来维持军纪，并不简单
...is sitting on your butt to keep warm.
对面的德军在干什么？
What are the Germans doing?
同样的事，他们没有火
Same damn thing, except they don't have any heat.
他们得运动来保持暖和
They gotta exercise to keep from freezing.
我对你的人也带来一点小运动
Well, I got a little exercise for your boys.
我今晚要派巡逻队 抓战俘回来
I wanna patrol tonight, try to pick up some prisoners.
好，我来安排
Well, there they are.
- 上士，把那些毡子装回去  - 别这样，把窗户封起来
- Hey, sarge, put those blankets back.  - Come on, shut the window.
你为何要那么做？ 上士
What do you wanna do that for, sarge?
你知道那超过射程 只会招惹较大火力的还击而已
They're out of range. They'll shoot back with something heavier.
是你和他们，狗脸 我需要练习
It's you or them, dogface. I need practice.
够了，上士，
That's enough, sergeant.
想玩射击游戏 就到外面去
If you wanna play with that popgun, you can go outside.
你认为我带人去打野外如何？ 少尉
What do you say I take the men out for a field drill, lieutenant?
在这种天气下 为了什么呢？
In this weather? What for?
因为他们在操练 那就是为什么
Because they're drilling, that's why.
我想出操时会让你知道，上士
I'll let you know when I want a drill, sergeant.
是的，长官，少尉
Yes, sir, lieutenant.
我要那个上士
I'll take that sergeant.
好，那没关系 但你其他的志愿者由我挑选
All right. That's all right. But I'll pick the rest of your volunteers.
你的，中校
Here you are, colonel.
我们在天黑前还有三个小时 来点一半一半如何？
We got about three hours before dark. How about some half-and-half?
只要加一点点就行了
Just sweeten it.
稍候
你是海斯勒上校？
You are Colonel Hessler?
你是谁？
Who are you?
你是怎么进来这里的？
How did you get in here?
科勒将军的签字是魔术
General Kohler's signature is magic.
请原谅我们失陪，少校
You will excuse us, major.
在你下命令之前 我能问你的阶级吗？
Before you give orders, may I ask your rank?
一级交际花
Courtesan, first class.
科勒将军的致意
Compliments of General Kohler.
我想我们都谈到了，上校
I think we have covered everything, colonel.
科勒将军没告诉我你这么帅！
General Kohler did not tell me you were so handsome.
科勒将军对我的事 告诉你些什么
What did General Kohler tell you about me?
什么都没说
Nothing.
任何我想知道的事
Whatever I want to know...
我会自己去发掘
...l'll find out for myself.
对那方面我很在行
I'm very good at that.
你不请我喝杯酒吗？
Aren't you going to offer me a drink?
还是你在前线待的太久 忘了礼貌
Or have you been at the front so long you have forgotten your manners?
我们聊些什么？
What shall we talk about?
也许聊你太太
Your wife perhaps.
你不与我一块喝吗？
Won't you join me?
有人说我是个有魅力的女人
I am told I'm an attractive woman.
而你对我并不太注意
You are not paying much attention to me.
能逃过我注意的非常少
Very little has escaped my attention.
科勒将军的确告诉我一件事
General Kohler did tell me one thing.
他最钦佩你的是 你在女人方面的名声
What he admires most about you is your reputation with the ladies.
真遗憾 我的指挥官对我是这个看法
I regret that is the opinion of my commanding officer.
我非常努力的保持 我是军人之名
I have worked very hard to achieve a reputation as a soldier.
我们两不能在一起了吗？
Do not the two go together?
转达将军，他的好意我心领了
Give the general my compliments. Tell him, "Thank you.
晚安
I appreciate his gesture." And good night.
你能自己走出去
You can make your own way out.
距攻击发起时间还有2小时
Zero minus two hours.
各部队预备攻击
All units ready to attack.
重复:距攻击发起时间 有2小时 各部队预备攻击
Repeat. Zero minus two hours. All units ready to attack.
- 快点！快点！  - 把手放下来，德国人
- Come on.  - Put them down, dummkopf.
哈！凯利
Hello, Kiley.
我很好奇你如何侦讯你的战俘
I was curious to see how you interrogate your prisoners.
我其他的军官也许问错了问题
My other officers may be asking the wrong questions.
我恐怕不会有新的答案
I'm afraid you won't hear any new answers.
有时候你看到的较他们所说的更来的重要
Sometimes it's more important what you see than what they say.
这里能亮一点吗？
Could we get a little more light in here?
这样行吗？ 长官
How's that, sir?
这就是不败之师的面孔
So this is the face of the undefeated enemy.
看起来像是 星期天主日学上抓的
It looks like you've captured a Sunday school class.
这是他们剩下 能放在前线的吗？ 他们武器在那？
This all they have left to put in the front lines? Where are the weapons?
在这，长官
Here, sir.
这是什么？
What's this?
枪膛里还有黄油 这从未射击过
Still has grease in the barrel. It's never been fired.
- 他们有开枪吗？  - 没有，长官
- Did they put up any fight?  - No, sir.
只是投降？
Just gave up.
我不感到惊异，他们只是孩子
Well, I'm not surprised. They're only children.
仔细的看看他们，凯利
Take a good look at them, Kiley.
他们甚至不够强悍到能被视为不良少年
They're not even tough enough to be classified as delinquents.
问他们吗？ 他们是否会赢得战争
Go ahead and question them. Ask if Germany's gonna win the war.
问吧！凯利
Go ahead, Kiley.
他们可能是计划这么做的 以便误导我们
They could be plants put in the front lines to mislead us.
我要单独和你谈谈，凯利
I want to talk to you alone, Kiley.
护送这些战俘接受适当的侦讯
Escort these prisoners to the rear for proper interrogation.
是的，长官，把他们带出去
Yes, sir. Move them out.
- 好了、我们走、走！  - 出发！
- Let's go, move it out.  - Go!
长官 所有的战俘都带着橡胶管
These prisoners were carrying these rubber hoses.
一起送去 及任何他们带的东西
Send them along, and anything else you found.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
你事实上仍然想着 德军在准备一次主要的攻击
Do you actually still think the Germans are preparing a major offensive?
是的，长官，上校，我认为
Yes, sir, colonel, I do.
你是说你所抓到的那些孩子 只是替换调到后方整编
You mean those kids are replacements for more seasoned troops...
预备较大攻击之精锐部队的人
...sent to the rear to re-form for the big attack?
是的，长官，上校，我认为
Yes, sir, colonel, I do.
凯利，你疯了 事实对你没有任何意义 证据对你没有任何意义
Kiley, you're crazy. Facts mean nothing to you. Evidence means nothing.
唯一对你是重要的是 你的烂预感
The only thing you can see are your own cockeyed hunches.
但那在军中是没用的
Well, that doesn't work in the Army.
我推荐你调到华府去坐办公桌
I'm recommending you for transfer to a desk in Washington.
你可以告诉总统 要如何打这场仗
You can tell the president how to run the war.
少校
Major.
你与我妻子一样不会泡咖啡
You make coffee as bad as my wife.
她总是告诉我 我不能在军队里好好生活
She always told me I'd never get along in the Army.
我在警察局里从未那么轻松
I never had it so easy in the police force.
我错了很多次
I've just been counting up how many times I've been wrong.
但这次绝对不会错
But never this wrong.
所有迹象指明一点
All the signs point to only one thing.
或许他们有别的企图吗？
Is it possible they mean something else?
或许我无法胜任这次战争又或许上校是对的
Maybe this war is beyond me and maybe Colonel Pritchard's right.
从总部来的，给你的
Runner brought this from headquarters. It's for you.
打开
Open it.
是德军上校和他的记录照片
Well, it's a picture of a Kraut colonel and his service record.
是我要的
I wanted that.
这个也是，坦克指挥官，五次作战纪录
Well, there it is again. Panzer officer. Fine fighting record.
最后一次是在苏联前线指挥坦克团
Last reported in the Russian front commanding a tank regiment.
他在干吗？
What's he doing here?
证明了我的观点
I'd say that proves my point.
他在苏联打了败仗之后就被解职了
Colonel Pritchard would probably say he got fired for losing the war in Russia.
我不知道，你觉得呢？
I don't know. What do you think?
长官，我是在正规军队我没与上校们打交道
Well, sir. I'm regular Army. I don't get into beefs between colonels.
但我可以告诉你一些狂人的想法
But I'll tell you what some of my stir-crazy men think.
他们认为我们在此有很大机会
They think we got a great opportunity here.
我们有机会横扫德国
We got a chance to wipe out Germany.
从地图上横扫，销毁一切
Just wipe it clean off the map. Knock everything down...
每座城市
...every city...
每个城堡，每座桥梁每条道路，一切
...every castle, all the bridges, all the roads. Everything.
别留下两块放在一起的石头把表面扫干净
Don't leave two stones standing together. Just wipe the slate clean.
把德国变成大草原然后运些水牛过来
Turn Germany into a prairie, then ship over a few buffalo...
让他们开始抓爬
...and let them start from scratch.
你觉得如何，上校？
Now, what do you think of that, colonel?
我觉得你们那些人需要洗洗袜子，刮刮胡子，太臭了
I think your men ought to wash their socks and take a shave. It stinks in here.
（德文）
- 说英文，只准说英文  - 是的，少尉
- Speak English. Only English.  - Okay, lieutenant.
让我们把这些东西弄离开这里
Let's get this stuff out of here.
空军呼叫OB！空军呼叫OB
特遣队空降敌线之后
Operation Transit parachuted behind enemy lines.
重复:特遣队空降敌线之后
Repeat. Operation Transit parachuted behind enemy lines.
十，九，八，七，六
五，四，三，二，一
零
是什…
What the...?
那是什么声音？
What's that noise?
起来，大家都到外面来
On your feet! Everybody out!
- 听起来像是有几千辆  - 查理！接通营部
- Sounds like a thousand of them.  - Hey, Charlie, get battalion.
- 接营部  - 快点！快点！
- Get battalion.  - On the double! On the double!
上士！叫大家都出来
Sergeant, haul everybody out.
- 大家都出来  - 各排长向我报到
- Everybody out. Come on.  - Bazooka men, report to me.
线路不通，长官
The line's dead, sir.
走…走！
Go! Go! Go!
那是什么？
What's that?
那是什么？ 你想看德国人，对吧
"What's that?" And you wanted to see Germans, right?
到外面去，快点
Come on! On the double!
快点
On the double!
调头！调头！我们走！ 我们走…我们走！
Turn them over! Turn them over! Let's go! Let's go!
快点！快点！ 我们开到前面去！
Come on, let's get this baby moving.
海斯勒上校报告 坦克出发攻击了
Colonel Hessler reports panzer Tiger moving to the attack.
没有敌人活动
No enemy activity.
北方前线报告 坦克已进入罗森湾
Northern front reporting panzer Eisen entering Losheim Gap.
没遭到任何敌人的抵抗
No enemy opposition encountered.
南方前线报告
Southern front reporting.
所有的坦克 全都在座标02的 十字路口集结
All elements of panzer Eisen linking up at road junction 0-2.
紧跟着我
Stay on my tail.
士兵
Soldier.
他们给你基本训练吗？
Did they give you basic training?
拿着！ 你要这么做！
Here, you do it this way.
菜鸟！从未看过战争场面 你还能期待什么？
They're green, never seen action before. What do you expect?
上士 没有命令没有人能够动
Sergeant, you're the anchorman here. Nobody moves without orders.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
你会发现多一个人在这 不会有任何差别的
Stay here. One more man won't make a difference.
- 我需要看那虎型坦克的内部  - 好的，来吧！
- I need to look inside one of those Tigers.  - All right, come on.
海斯勒呼叫OB 遭遇敌人，
Relay to Standard O-bay. I've made contact with enemy.
受到轻微抵抗
Meeting weak resistance.
找掩护！设法抵挡 找掩护！设法抵挡
Take cover! Make a stand. Take cover! Make a stand.
设法抵挡
Make a stand.
填弹！
Load.
我说填弹！
I said, load!
老虎对104号坦克 104号坦克，你挡住路了
Tiger to Tank 104. Tank 104, you're blocking the road.
立刻离开路面！
Get off the road at once!
那就是你的虎型坦克
There's your Tiger.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你会需要这个
You're gonna need this.
带着那冲锋枪
Take the greaser.
老虎呼叫104号坦克 你的情况如何？
Tiger to Tank 104, what is your condition?
104号坦克，立刻回答
Tank 104, reply at once.
我是海斯勒上校
This is Colonel Hessler.
关顶盖
Button up!
虎型坦克在11点方向
Tigers at 11 o'clock.
干掉他们！艾迪
Hit them hard, Eddie.
他们干掉布朗迪了
They got Blondie.
算了 就像是用网球打它们
Forget it. It's like hitting them with tennis balls.
我们离开这里！
Come on, let's get out of here!
保持低姿势
Get down and stay down.
笨蛋！用爬的
Crawl, you dummy! Crawl.
少尉，继续拿枪榴弹来
Lieutenant, keep those grenades coming.
撤退！
Fall back!
趴下！
Get down.
保持低姿势！保持低姿势！
Get going. Stay low.
海斯勒呼叫总部
Hessler to headquarters.
抵抗非常的轻微
Resistance very weak.
南方前线报告
Southern front reporting.
海斯勒指挥官遭到轻微的抵抗
Commander Nimke encountering light resistance.
敌人正越过K1O河退却中
Enemy retreating across river K- 10.
- 少尉 我们离开这里  - 来个人协助操作这挺机枪
- Let's get out of here.  - Hey, somebody man this gun!
- 他们来了  - 射击！他们来了
- Here they come!  - There they are!
拿弹带来
Give me a belt!
等等我！
Hey, wait for me!
抓住车边
Grab the tailgate!
等等我！
Wait for me!
- 你的车辆调度场在那？  - 在团里，离此地四公里
- Where's your motor pool?  - At regiment, four kilometers.
我们到那去，我得赶回师部
Let's get there. I gotta get back to headquarters.
- 等等我  - 慢一点
- Wait for me!  - Hold it a minute!
等等我
Wait for me!
我们没机会了
We haven't got a chance.
放松
Relax. Stay loose.
你认为我们得投降？
You think we'll have to surrender?
我听说他们对待美国俘虏很好
Well, I hear they treat American prisoners real well.
在战斗中，他们对谁都不好
In a big battle, they treat nobody real well.
有一条后路
Come on. There's a back road that leads to the motor pool.
- 或许我们能得到一辆吉普  - 你如何知道？
- Maybe we can get us a jeep.  - How do you know?
因为我来此之前研究过地图
Because I studied the maps when we arrived here.
就如你该做的
Just like you should've done.
- 若我们走入线内呢？  - 我们仍在他们前头
- What if we run into their lines?  - We're still ahead of them.
- 他们可能有高级巡逻队  - 要保住性命真麻烦
- They might have advanced patrols.  - It's enough trouble keeping alive...
在这种混乱的形势下
...in this mess without you bellyaching.
若你想投降，尽管去 我一个人轻松一点
If you wanna surrender, go ahead. I'll make it easier alone.
你出线了
You're out of line, sergeant.
对不起，中尉
Sorry, lieutenant.
我不需要你的帮助 你自己前进
Look, I don't need help from you. You wanna go on by yourself, go ahead.
你来吗？ 我要背你吗？
Are you coming, or am I gonna have to carry you?
哈，夏安
Hello, Cheyenne.
什么？ 你被攻击了
What's that? You're under attack?
什么样的兵力？
In what strength?
那你推测呢？
Well, what's your guess?
我不能给你空中侦察 气候太差,无法侦查!
I can't give you air reconnaissance, I'm blind.
- 接“阿帕奇”  - 呼叫“阿帕奇”
- Get Apache.  - Call Apache.
哈，艾迪，你那区如何？
Eddie, what's going on in your sector?
只有巡逻队的接战 有多强大？
It's only patrol action. How heavy?
你的侦察部队怎么说？ 没有任何大规模的
Well, what does your reconnaissance say? Nothing heavy.
我不知道，正试着了解全盘 保持联络
We're trying to get a picture. Stay on task.
我们的第一阶段进攻取得了成功。
The first phase of our offensive was a success.
奇袭的效果完成了
The element of surprise was complete.
美军的通信有如在矿坑一般
American communications are in a turmoil.
但我们得在美军了解 我们是全面攻击之前
We must cross the Our River before the enemy realizes...
先占领瓦尔桥
...we have launched an all-out offensive.
我相信我没准许你抽烟！
I do not believe I gave you permission to smoke.
抱歉，长官
Sorry, sir.
我们没能有时间相处 非常的不幸
Unfortunately, we did not have time to get better acquainted...
但你们全都了解我的名声
...but all of you know my reputation.
我的部队永远是有最多的死伤
My command always suffers the highest casualties.
胜利的代价从来不便宜
The price of victory is never cheap.
这次的战役我们会像我们的坦克一般的坚硬！
In this battle, we will be as hard as our tanks.
我会完成派给我的任务
I will reach the objectives assigned to me...
不计一切的代价！
...no matter what the cost.
总部来的电讯，指挥官
Signal from headquarters, colonel.
海斯勒，我恭喜你！
Hessler, I congratulate you.
- 你依照着计划的时间  - 我会如同计划的到达鲁尔桥
- You're on schedule.  - I will reach the Our River as planned.
但一定不能让敌人炸毁那座桥
But the enemy must not be permitted to destroy the bridge.
- 特遣队占领了它没有？  - 还没有
- Has Schumacher seized it yet?  - Not yet.
特遣队首要的任务是破坏敌人的通信
Schumacher's primary assignment is to disrupt enemy communications.
我必须要为我的坦克巩固那座桥的安全
I must have that bridge secured for my tanks.
我没有时间架桥
I have no time to build bridges.
海斯勒 你的桥会确保安全的
Hessler, your bridge will be secured.
我们期待根据 你时间表经过它！
We are expecting you to cross it according to the schedule.
你们晓得我们前进的路线？ 配合地图研究吧？
You know your line of march. Coordinate with the map.
康拉德！我头痛！
Conrad, I have a headache.
着火了 着火了
Fire! Fire!
地雷？ 它们为何没被清除掉？
Land mines! Why were they not cleared?
带地雷侦测器的人呢？
Where are the men with mine detectors?
我们前进的太快，
We are moving too fast.
他们跟不上
The men are following in trucks.
他们全死了
They are all dead.
地雷在他们底下爆炸
The mine exploded directly under them.
叫副连长接管，告诉他们
Notify their seconds-in-command to take over.
我对他们有绝对的信心！
Tell them I have absolute confidence in them.
我们不必要的损失了坦克
We have lost a tank unnecessarily.
我们不必要的损失了 宝贵的时间
We've lost precious minutes unnecessarily.
你有责任要保护这型坦克
Your troops were here to protect the panzers.
从现在起到我们清理完 这地雷区
From now on, until we clear this minefield...
你的人要走在我的坦车之前
...your men will go ahead of my tanks.
而且立刻修好我的指挥车！
And have my vehicle repaired at once!
快点！继续走！跟上去
Come on, keep moving. Step on it.
现在！听我说！你们全部！
Now, listen to me, all of you.
我需要准确的情报
I need precise information:
有多少人，敌人投入这次攻击
How many men, how many guns...
多少大炮，多少坦克
...how many tanks the enemy are throwing into this.
他们有多少燃料携行？ 而且查清楚
How much fuel are they carrying? And get a move on.
在我们大叫救命前有24小时
We've got 24 hours before we scream rape.
好了，凯利！轮到你了
All right, Kiley, it's your turn.
他们突破而过，将军
They're pouring through, general.
精锐的部队，全新的装备
Crack troops. Brand-new equipment.
我看了他们坦克的内部 我们现有装备无法与之匹敌！
I looked inside one of their tanks. They can chew up anything we've got.
- 问题是，他们要去哪里？  - 你有那情报？ 凯利
- Question is, where are they going?  - Do you have that information?
没有，长官，但是他有 海斯勒上校
No, but he does. Colonel Hessler...
我发现他是坦克的指挥官
...the commanding officer of the panzer spearhead.
当我们知道他去那时
When we know where he's going...
我们就知道整个 德军攻击的目标
...we'll know the objective of the attack.
敌军在85哩前线中 突破了五处
The enemy is probing at five points along an 85-mile front.
在只有那些情报能分析处理下
With only that information at our disposal...
你如何能说海斯勒的旅是前锋
...how can you assume Hessler's column is the spearhead?
- 法律的可能性？ 凯利  - 不，长官
- The law of probability, Kiley?  - No, sir.
法律的可能性反对我
The law of probability is against me.
但是既然没有其他的情报 我有五分之一的机会是对的
But in the absence of other information, I've one chance in five of being right.
- 而我想赌赌那个机会  - 怎么做
- I'd like to explore that chance.  - How?
- 这个，长官  - 我告诉你怎么做
- Well, sir...  - I'll tell you how.
看着瓦尔河
Watch the Our River.
只有在这里的一座桥 能支持重型坦克
There's only one bridge, right here, that can support heavy tanks.
我说那是海斯勒要去的地方 也是我要去的地方
I'd say that's where Hessler will be, and that's where I'll be.
凯利！ 别太接近那座桥 我下令炸掉它
Don't get too close to that bridge. I've ordered it blown up.
能知道太好了，谢谢你的消息
That's a good thing to know. Thanks for the tip.
继续走…继续走！ 快点！继续走！
Keep moving. Keep moving. Keep moving. Go on, keep moving.
快点！我们走 继续走！
Come on, let's go. You there, keep moving.
-快点！我们走！  - 快点！
- Come on, let's go.  - Come on.
快点！快点！我们走！
Come on. Come on, let's go.
我们走！你还在等什么？
Let's go. What are you waiting for?
快点！继续走！ 快点！我们走！
Move it. Come on, keep moving. Step on it. Get going.
好了！快走！跟上前面的
Come on, let's get going. Step on it.
（安不列芙…36公里）
你停下来干什么？
Hey, what are you stopping for?
那个路标 我们以前也走过呀！
That sign. When we came through before...
- 我记得安不列芙是往那条路走  - 你们挡住路了，快走！
- ...I recall Ambleve was that way.  - You're blocking the road. Get going.
- 快点！  - 来吧！我们走
- Hurry up.  - Come on, let's go.
且慢 我告诉你那路标方向错了
Wait a minute. I tell you, those signs point in the wrong direction.
是什么阻挡了这次的行进？
What's holding up the parade here?
有人对路标做了手脚，少尉
Somebody's been monkeying around with those road signs.
那不是去安不列芙的路
That ain't the road to Ambleve.
两小时前我由安不列芙来
Two hours ago, I came here from Ambleve...
走的是一模一样的路
...over this exact same road.
也许他们同时把 安不列芙移动了
Now, maybe they've moved Ambleve in the meantime...
但两小时前这是去那的路
...but two hours ago this was the road to it.
- 走吧！杜金  - 少尉，我在告诉你…
- Take off, Duquesne.  - Lieutenant, I'm telling you...
少尉！叫你的上士 把吉普车开走好吗？
Lieutenant, tell your sergeant to get this jeep out of here.
走！这是命令！走！
Move. That's an order. Move.
是，希望他在美乐地玩的愉快
Yeah, I hope they enjoy themselves in Malmedy.
- 来吧！我们在这下车  - 等一下
- Come on. We're getting off here.  - Wait.
来吧！
Come on!
跳
Jump.
等一下，等一下，我们去那？
Hey, wait a minute. Where we going?
我们应该到安不列芙去的 你晓得我们的营部在那
We're supposed to be in Ambleve.
闭嘴！我们会到那的 我们得先去取点货
We'll get there. I gotta make a pickup first.
- 取货？取哪类的货  - 我在路旁的农舍放了一些货
- Pickup?  - I got some merchandise in a farmhouse.
但德军要来了 他们会偷走它的 你得来帮帮我，来吧！
Germans are coming. They'll steal it. You gotta give me a hand.
你们两个
Hey, you two!
快点！继续走，跟着前面的
Come on, keep moving. Step on it.
你是最后一辆了吗？ 你后面有任何人吗？
Are you the last one? Anybody behind you?
有，整个德军！走吧！
Yeah, the whole German army. Go ahead.
你！继续走！快点！ 跟着前面的
You there, keep them moving. Come on, step on it.
通知坦克，桥安然无恙
Notify the panzers. The bridge is intact.
呼叫，呼叫，桥安然无恙
桥安然无恙
- 有德军的踪影吗？  - 还没有
- Any sign of the Germans?  - No, not yet.
- 你们到这来干什么  - 我们奉令炸桥，
- What are you men doing here?  - We got orders to blow the bridge.
- 下车  - 等一下，中尉
- Pile out.  - Wait a minute.
桥已经在装炸药了
That job's being done.
你们弄的怎么样了
How you boys making out?
- 快弄好了  - 快一点，好吗？
- Just about finished.  - Hurry up, will you?
你们最好在德军来之前 离开这里
Get out of here before those Krauts get here.
- 你们需要帮忙吗？  - 我有个好主意
- You need any help?  - I got a good idea.
我们把所有的热水瓶给他们 那些水刚由冰上收集的
We'll give them all a hot-water bottle. That water comes straight off the ice.
我有一车的C4炸药 需要用吗？
Well, I'm sure loaded with C-4. Can you use any?
我想我能卖一些给你
I imagine they could sell you some.
开车
Climb in.
你接引爆器的电线 是谁给你们的
Hey, why do you got your wires hooked on to that detonator?
- 我想他太快...  - 去送命吗？ 不是那种方法
- I guess he's in a hurry.  - To get killed? That's not the way.
中士，带几个你的人
Sarge, bring a couple of men.
我们要去看看那座桥的底下
We're gonna take a look under that bridge.
这不是去安不列芙的路 这是去美乐地的路
This ain't the road to Ambleve.
路标是这么说的
That's what the sign says.
路标说是那条路 地图说是这条
The sign says thataway, the map says Ambleve was this way.
有人的工作没做好
Will somebody straighten this out?
安不列芙，安不列芙
Ambleve. Ambleve.
- 乌兰斯基  - 中校
- Hey, Wolenski.  - Oh, colonel.
路在这弄不清楚了
Hey, we're all fouled up here.
我们奉命到安不列芙去 但地图和路标不一样
We've been ordered to Ambleve, but the maps don't jibe with the signs.
你开始就走错路了 这是去美乐地的路
How'd you get off the road? This will take you to Malmedy.
- 安不列芙是那一条  - 那条路？
- Ambleve's that way.  - That way?
我们一直跟着路标在走
We've been following these road signs the whole way.
而且我们遇到的宪兵 也指挥我们走这条路
And the MPs we ran into, they've been directing us this way.
它们改过了，被人调换过了
They've been changed. They switched them around.
你遇到的那些宪兵看起来没有问题吧
Those MPs you ran into seem okay?
- 此话怎讲  - 他们有任何怪异的地方吗？
- What do you mean?  - Anything odd about them?
只是普通的大兵
Just regular Gls.
我们几天前截到敌人的情报
We intercepted an enemy dispatch.
他们在招募说英文的德军
They were recruiting English-speaking Germans.
你什么时候度过瓦尔桥的
What time did you cross the Our River?
八点40分 我们是最后一辆车 我听他们说要炸桥
8:40. We were last ones across. They were set to blow it.
- 你看到桥被炸掉？  - 没
- You see the bridge blown?  - No.
但我看到工兵在装炸药
But I saw the engineers setting the charges.
等一等，怎么回事 他们不是工兵，是宪兵
Hey, wait a minute. What the hell? They weren't engineers, they were MPs.
墨菲，给我接师部
Murphy, get me headquarters.
少校，叫人把路标换回来
And, major, have someone switch that sign back.
红河六号，请回答，红河六号
Red River Six. Come in, Red River Six.
- 请讲话，红河二号  - 红河六号，这是红河二号
- Come in, Red River Two.  - Red River Six, this is Red River Two.
德军扮成美军宪兵 控制了瓦尔桥
Germans uniformed as American MPs holding Our River Bridge.
桥没有被炸掉
Bridge has not been blown.
重覆，德军扮成 美军宪兵
Repeat. Germans uniformed as American MPs...
控制瓦尔桥 桥没有被炸掉
...holding Our River Bridge. Bridge has not been blown.
通话完毕 我们走
Over and out. Let's go.
停下来，杰克
Better hold it, Jack.
- 发生了什么事  - 他们遭遇了德军巡逻队的战斗
- What happened?  - They ran into a firefight. German patrol.
我没看到任何德国人
I don't see any Germans.
他们在河里，他们没渡过来
They're in the river. They didn't make it across.
快离开这，要炸桥了
Get out of here. We're blowing the bridge.
什么？你确定吗？
What? Are you sure?
小心，宪兵是伪装的
Watch out, the MPs are Krauts!
我的天，下来
Oh, my God! Get down!
我们在等什么？ 把那坦克弄走
Why are we waiting? Get that tank out of the way.
我们现在预备拖走了，长官
We are preparing to tow it off now, sir.
老虎对豹营前锋 把那坦克由桥上轰掉
Tiger to tanks Leopard and Panther. Blast that tank off the bridge.
是总部，上校
It's headquarters, colonel.
科勒将军说我们时间落后了
General Kohler says we are behind schedule.
他要知道是什么拖延我们了
He wants to know what's holding us up.
告诉将军 美军学会了如何撤退
Tell the general the Americans are learning how to retreat.
老虎对豹营 上桥把那废物推开
Tiger to Panther. Get onto the bridge, push that junk right out of the way.
保持低姿势
Stay down.
墨菲 通知师部瓦尔桥没被炸掉
Murphy, call headquarters. Tell them the Our River Bridge hasn't been blown.
- 敌军大部队正在通过  - 是的，长官
- The enemy's crossing in great strength.  - Yes, sir.
- 把步枪给我  - 你需要的是大炮，长官
- Let me have your rifle.  - What you need is a cannon, sir.
我上次看到那德军时 我有的只是架照相机
The last time I saw that German, all I had was a camera.
你不能快一点吗？ 上士 我们快跟不上部队了
Can't you hurry it up, sergeant? We lost the column.
你凑巧在口袋里 有个新化油器吗？ 少尉
Do you happen to have a new carburetor in your pocket, lieutenant?
你是说我们卡在这了
You mean we're stuck here?
不，我们还可以用走的
Nope. We can still walk.
我们走
Let's go.
- 也许我们能搭便车  - 站住
- Hey, maybe we can get a lift, huh?  - Hold it.
我们最好先弄清楚他们是谁
We better find out just who they are first.
头低下
Down.
是德国人，退后
Yeah, Krauts. Back.
若是你能放轻松点 我能把他们全干掉的
If you'd just stayed loose, I could've gotten them all.
美军退却中 我军在所有的前线都节节胜利
Americans in headlong retreat. Our forces are advancing on all fronts.
俘获许多的战俘
Great numbers of prisoners are being taken.
我对这件事有不良的预感
I got a bad feeling about this.
你想脱逃，为何不跑呢
If you wanted to make a run for it, why didn't you?
我是你的排副，少尉
I'm in your outfit, lieutenant.
我的职责是照顾你 到你去的地方去
My job is to look out for you, go where you go.
这一次的确把你弄到 错误的地方
I sure got you into the wrong place this time.
我…我很高兴你和我在一起
But I'm glad you're with me.
当我们到达战俘营时会被分开
When we get to the POW camp, they'll separate us...
你会到军官区的
...you being an officer.
是的
Yeah.
我会想念你的，上士
I'm gonna miss you, sergeant.
跑
Run!
继续跑
Keep going!
继续走，快点，快点
Get going. Come on, step on it.
- 露易丝在这吗？  - 不在
- Is she here?  - No.
那么告诉她我回来了，好吗？
Well, tell her I'm back, huh?
我要你们去把本部队的人全都能找出来
I want you all to fan out. Round up every man that belongs to this outfit.
我们十分钟后在这里集合 快点去
We will assemble here in 10 minutes. On the double.
我们走
Let's go.
这是什么
What's all this?
看起来像什么？ 我作生意的地方
What's it look like? My place of business.
- 这些鸡是干什么的  - 它们生蛋
- What are the chickens for?  - They lay eggs.
你知道现在新鲜鸡蛋 是什么价钱
Any idea what fresh eggs brings in these days?
太美了，太美了
Oh, beautiful, beautiful.
去开门，那是我的拍档
All right, open the door, that's my partner.
听着 查清楚我们的战车停在那
Look, run down to the tank park and check us both in.
- 但…  - 何时出发 然后再来找我，去吧
- But...  - And then report back to me. Go ahead.
这些鸡看起好瘦 你有按时喂吗？
The chickens look scrawny. Have you been feeding them regular?
我在担心你
I was worried about you.
- 德国人要来了是不是真的  - 是，正好经过这
- Is it true the Germans are coming?  - Right through here.
- 我们得赶快把一切都卖了  - 然后你就要走了
- We gotta sell everything, fast.  - Then you'll leave?
我们面对它吧 我们生意作不成了 一箱香槟360元
Face it, kid, we're out of business. One case of champagne, $360.
两打玻璃丝袜80元 20瓶香水200元
Two dozen nylons, $80. Twenty bottles of perfume, $200.
6百…40元 这是你那一半，
Six hundred and forty dollars. Here's your half.
320元 你作了多少
Three hundred and twenty dollars. All right, what did you make?
1230元，在这
One thousand, two hundred and thirty dollars. Here.
你在卖些什么？ 没看到卖多少货
What have you been selling? I don't see much stock gone.
- 拿去  - 在我知道你是怎么挣的之前
- Take it.  - I won't until I know how you made it.
- 我不会拿的 你以为我是什么人  - 你以为我是什么人
- What do you think I am?  - What do you think I am?
- 这些钱是我为我们存的  - 为我们？ 你在说些什么
- It's money I've saved for us.  - For us? What are you talking about?
当一个女人 和一个男的合伙挣钱 她的意思是永远
When a woman goes in business with a man, it means forever.
什么是永远？ 店关了，德军来了
What's forever? The shop is closed. The Germans are coming.
他们以前来这过
They've been here before.
我活过来了
I've lived through it.
我会再活过来的
I will live through it again.
我会等你的
I will wait for you.
你为何会对我有这种感觉 我碰都没碰过你
How can you feel this way about me? I never laid a hand on you.
那就是原因
That's why.
你爱上我了
You're in love with me.
稍候，慢一点
Just a second. Hold the phone.
等一等
Hold the phone, here.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你知道吗？
You know what?
你是对的
You're right.
这里
There.
所有的钱你保管 我得回去打仗
You hold all the money. I gotta go back in action.
你不晓得作战时是什么情况
You don't know what it's like in combat.
你知道，你中弹了 有人拿走你所有的钱
You get shot, somebody takes your money.
在卫生兵来到之前 那些人的手已伸进了你的口袋
Before the plasma comes, a guy's got his hand in your pocket.
葛菲，葛菲
Guffy. Guffy.
- 我不要你被杀  - 谁在说要被杀了？
- I don't want you to get killed.  - Who's talking about getting killed?
你保管钱
You take care of the money.
上士，坦克奉令后撤 来吧，我们得赶上它们
Sarge, the tanks aren't there. They've been pulled back. We gotta catch up.
葛菲
Guffy.
回头见，拍档
So long, partner.
保重
Take care of yourself.
葛菲
Guffy.
你不想吻我吗？
Don't you want to kiss me?
别忘了喂鸡
Don't forget to feed the chickens, huh?
继续走，我们走，继续走
Keep moving. Let's go, keep moving.
快点，上士，我们得赶上他们 我们走
Come on, sarge, we gotta catch up with the tanks. Let's go!
再见，露易丝
Goodbye, Louise!
把那个放在那里面
Put that in there.
快点，弄好它，弄好它
Come on, get to it. Get to it.
狮营，就炮轰位置
Lion Battalion, take up bombardment position.
豹营，待命
Panther Battalion, stand by.
- 发动  - 是的，长官
- Get started.  - Yes, sir.
- 站住，士兵，你要跑去那  - 德军来了
- Hold it. Where you running?  - The Germans are coming.
- 你的步枪呢 你的部队呢？  - 被俘
- Where's your rifle? Where's your outfit?  - Captured.
- 死了，不见了 全不见了  - 中士，挡下那个人
- Dead. Gone. They're all gone.  - Sergeant, stop that man!
他所做的我们正在做的别无二致
He's not doing anything we aren't.
我们留下
We're staying.
联络已经后撤的人
Countermand that order to fall back.
由现在此各部队就地抵抗
All units are to make a stand where they are and fight.
而那表示是每一个了 除了坦克
And that means everybody. Except tanks.
文书，炊事兵，参谋
Clerks, cooks, bakers, staff officers.
任何一个能拿枪使用的人
Anybody who can carry a rifle is to use it.
- 凯利  - 来吧，全都搬回来
- Kiley.  - Come on, bring it all in.
对我而言非常难以启齿 我错了
It's very difficult for me to say this. I was wrong.
- 下车，中士，全都下车  - 全都下车
- Sergeant, haul them out again.  - Everybody out.
快点，在等什么
Come on, what are you waiting for?
好了，中校 看来我们要留下了
Well, it looks like we're staying.
- 当我需要把步枪时 你似乎从来都没有  - 拿我的去吧
- I never have a rifle when I need one.  - Take mine.
- 国家送的  - 我待会还回来
- It's on the house.  - I'll return it later.
- 我们走  - 我们走，快点，快点
- Let's go!  - Let's go. Come on.
总部的电话，长官
We're on the line, sir.
我是葛雷将军 布雷德莱
General Grey speaking. Fred.
我守着安不列芙 但没有重武器我守不住
I'm holding at Ambleve, but I can't last without heavy stuff.
你能给我什么
What can you let me have?
155榴炮能挡的住 它们在哪？ 在平板车上
155s will do the trick. Where are they? On flatcars.
铁路还在我们手中？
Are we still holding the rail line?
好，你何时能让它们到这里？
Good. Now, when can you get them here?
不是待会，佛列得，指望你了
Well, not later, Fred. We're counting on you.
把那些拿上来
Bring that ammo up!
把那些东西拿来，堆在墙边
Stack it up. Position, on the wall.
把那些猪弄过来
Get some beef behind it.
叫些人待在它后面
Hey, lay those logs in there.
我们走，往前去
Let's go! Let's move it out.
第一排跟我走 第二排到那边去
First Platoon, follow me. Second Platoon, over there.
射击
Fire.
（圣诞快乐一美军进城了）
士兵们
Soldier!
往前去，往前去
Go! Go!
大家都出去
Everybody out!
- 等一等，等一等，你们要去哪  - 去防空壕去
- Wait a minute. Where you men going?  - To the shelter.
- 不，你们不去 脱掉围裙拿步枪  - 但我们是炊事兵
- No, you're not. Grab your rifles.  - But we're cooks.
午餐结束了，拿着步枪跟我来
Lunch is over. Get your rifles and follow me.
- 小心砖头，离建筑物远一点  - 快点，士兵，到前面去
- Stay away from the buildings!  - Soldier, up front.
我是伞兵
I'm in the Air Corps.
你现在是步兵了，跟我来
You're in the infantry now. Follow me.
我们打退他们了，他们在后撤
We're driving them back. They're running.
这只是第一回合
This is only the first round.
你为何停下来
Why have you stopped?
他们筑了工事，
They have dug in.
- 很强的防御  - 绕过去
- It's a very strong defense.  - Bypass it.
- 我考虑过那一点了  - 没什么好考虑的
- I have considered that.  - There's nothing to consider.
我们必须衡量我们的得失
We must measure what we might gain by what we might lose.
来吧
Come on.
在此刻你应该已经在 安不列芙以西十公里的地方了
You were to have been 10 kilometers west of Ambleve by this hour.
你为何还在这里
Why are you still here?
我第一次攻击失败了 我必须攻下安不列芙
My first attack failed. I must take Ambleve.
我们在浪费时间 时间不早了 你没有多少时间了
We are wasting time. Time, Hessler, you don't have much.
安不列芙此刻是个 孤立的囊中物 绕过它去
Ambleve is an isolated resistance. Go around it.
我们也包围了 巴斯东而绕了过去 做同样的事
We have surrounded and bypassed Bastogne. Do the same.
将军，再一小时天就黑了
General, it will be dark in one hour.
我要你允许我以全部军力夜袭
I want your permission for a night assault with all my armor.
海斯勒上校
Colonel Hessler...
你要脱离这次接战 而去执行你的任务，
...you will break off this engagement, proceed with your mission.
- 这是命令  - 是的，长官
- That's an order.  - Yes, sir.
将军，在你离开之前 我能给你看样东西吗？
General, before you go, may I show you something?
是什么
What is it?
一个巧克力蛋糕
A chocolate cake.
又怎样
Well?
从被俘的美军士兵那拿到的 还是新鲜的
It was taken from a captured American private. It's still fresh.
你若看那包装，将军 你会看到是由波士顿来的
If you will look at the wrapping, general, you will see it comes from Boston.
还有呢
And?
将军，你了解这表示什么意思
General, do you realize what this means?
那表示美国有燃料及飞机
It means that the Americans have fuel and planes...
运蛋糕越过大西洋
...to fly cake across the Atlantic Ocean.
他们没有被打败的信念
They have no conception of defeat.
我们在这有机会 击垮他们的士气
We have the opportunity here to break their morale...
摧毁他们的作战意识
...to destroy their will to fight.
那是你必须准许我 把安不列芙夷为平地的原因
That is why you must permit me to reduce Ambleve to ashes.
你有…到凌晨四点之前的时间
You have until 0400.
仅此而已
That is all.
我们已令他们的枪声沉寂 现在我们要攻击了
We have silenced their guns. Now we will attack.
你的步兵和我的坦克一起去
Your infantry will go in with my tanks.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
第二排去那边
Second Platoon, over there.
我们走！快点
Let's go. Move it out.
我们最好在合围之前快离开
We'd better get going, sir, before the town is completely surrounded.
我是否该派信差找 乌兰斯基少校叫他掩护撒退？
Shall I send a runner to Major Wolenski telling him to cover our withdrawal?
不 那种命令只能我亲自下
No, that's the kind of order I give to a man myself.
瞄准坦克
Aim at the trench!
瞄低一点，我们接近一点
Some more. Let's get closer.
再多拿些塑胶炸药来
Bring up some more plastique!
乌兰斯基少校
Major Wolenski!
将军
The general.
在那，进去，赶快 把弹药拿上来
Hurry up! Move that ammo up!
乌兰斯基，我们奉令撒退
Wolenski, we've been ordered out.
我需要时间尽力抢救东西 你的部队得掩护撒退
I'll need time to save what I can. Your outfit will have to cover the withdrawal.
- 他们现在已经打到面前了 长官  - 你尽你的力
- They're coming down the chimney, sir.  - Do what you can.
- 是，长官  - 走吧
- Yes, sir.  - Come on.
这把步枪我只是借你的
I only loaned you this rifle.
- 待会见了，少校  - 是，长官
- See you later, major.  - Yes, sir.
散开
Spread out.
把弹药拿来
Bring up ammo!
修女姐妹
Sister.
上校，打扰了
Colonel, excuse me.
我们在找一位能帮忙的人
We are looking for someone who can help.
说吧
Be brief.
教堂地窖里 有许多受伤的本地人
There are many wounded townspeople in the church cellar.
我们需要医药，纱布 你能分一点给我们吗？
We need medicine, bandages. Can you spare any?
我们没东西分给你
We have nothing to spare.
有虏获任何医疗用品都给 修女
If there are captured medical supplies, give them to the nuns.
是的，长官，跟我来
Yes, sir. Follow me.
他用这个开火
He fired with this.
珍
Jean, Jean, Jean!
别伤害他
Don't do anything to him, please.
这是孩子的父亲
This is the boy's father.
我求你了，他只是个小孩子
I beg you. He's just a little boy.
他是我的独生子
He's my only child.
别伤害他
Don't do anything to him, please.
放了这孩子
Release the boy.
珍
Jean.
杀死他爸爸
Shoot the father.
- 爸爸  - 不
- Papa! Papa!  - No!
上校
Colonel.
被俘的美国高级军官
The senior American officer taken prisoner...
请求与您谈话
...requests permission to speak with you.
- 他想干吗？  - 他只想与您谈
- What does he want?  - He'll only discuss it with you.
- 军衔？  - 少校
- Rank?  - Major.
- 给他两分钟时间  - 是，长官
- He has two minutes.  - Yes, sir.
康拉德
Conrad.
- 什么食物？  - 城中最好的食物
- What is this food?  - It's the best this town has to offer.
我告诉过你坦克实施汽油配给， 士兵实施食物配给
I told you, tanks run on petrol and soldiers run on rations.
我必须与士兵吃一样的东西， 以便了解他们能走多远. 拿走.
I must eat as my men do so I know how far they can go. Take it away.
- 康拉德  - 什么？
- Conrad.  - Yeah?
我的圣诞礼物，给你儿子的
My Christmas present, it's for your sons.
还有，你晋升为上士
Your promotion to first sergeant.
我替我儿子谢谢你
My sons thank you.
进来
Go in.
什么？
What is it?
上校，你抓到的逃兵告诉我
Colonel, stragglers you've captured tell me...
无助的美国俘虏被屠杀了
...that helpless American prisoners have been massacred.
- 在哪里？  - 美乐地
- Where?  - Malmedy.
作为高级军官，我无法控制我的属下， 除非得到你的保证，
And as senior officer, I can't control my men unless I have your assurance...
他们不会被杀害 我要你签署命令…
...they'll not be murdered. I want your signed order stating that my men...
声明我的属下会遵照日内瓦公约
...will be accorded the protection...
作为战俘受到保护
...guaranteed prisoners of war by the Geneva Convention.
除非我带这个命令回去， 否则俘虏会暴动
Unless I return with that order, colonel, the prisoners will riot.
无疑，你会杀了我们， 但请帮我...
Undoubtedly, you'll kill us, but so help me...
...否则我们会拖上你们很多人垫背
...we'll take a hell of a lot of you with us.
不会签这个命令， 也不能有暴动
There will be no signed order. There will be no riot.
你不会被允许回去煽动暴动
You will not be allowed to return to your men to instigate that riot.
你听我说，上校
You listen to me, colonel.
任何大屠杀都会有生还者
There are survivors in all massacres.
我警告你，若我的人被伤害
I warn you, if any of my men are harmed...
你要负责任，你无处可逃
...you will be held responsible. There will be no place on earth that you can hide.
当找到你时，我希望是由我将你问吊
And when you're found, I hope I'm the man that ties the rope around your neck.
少校
Major...
我从不喜欢被威胁
...I have never liked threats.
我不会杀俘虏的
I do not kill prisoners.
但我如果因为你的最后一句话而亲手杀你，我不会有悔恨
But I will have no compunction at shooting you myself for your last remark.
那就杀了我吧
Then do it.
你是故意想惹我
You are deliberately trying to provoke me.
没错，上校
Yes, colonel, that's right.
若我活着走出去我知道我的人会被善待
If I walk out of here alive, I know my men will be properly treated.
迪波
Diepel!
把这位军官送回关押处 活着的
Return this officer to the prisoners' compound, alive.
走
Come.
我要你使你的人放心
Major, I'm relying on you to reassure your men...
我没时间对付烦人的俘虏
...I have no time for troublesome prisoners.
老虎呼叫OB，科勒将军
Tiger to Standard O-bay, General Kohler.
你的例行配给
Your usual ration, sir.
科勒将军
General Kohler. Hessler.
将军，美国俘虏在美乐地被杀害的消息是真的吗？
General, is it true that American prisoners were executed at Malmedy?
美乐地有党卫军部队
There are SS units in the Malmedy sector.
我无法为前线每一个士兵负责任
I can't assume responsibility for every soldier on this front.
你明白这种行为的后果吗？
Do you realize the consequences of this act?
为了安不列芙，我损失了17辆坦克，一队人马
I have lost 17 tanks and a battalion of men leveling Ambleve...
就因为打垮敌军的士气
...for the sole purpose of reducing the enemy's will to fight.
屠杀会使我们更加充满反抗之心
This massacre will stiffen resistance to us everywhere.
这会使一群匪徒变成复仇的战士
It will turn a demoralized mob into avenging soldiers.
你很无礼，上校
You are being insolent, colonel.
关心你自己的任务吧
Concern yourself with your mission.
你明天下午4点要达到圣米歇
You are to reach Saint-Michel by 1600 tomorrow.
- 到那里  - 是的，长官
- Be there.  - Yes, sir.
他们接受的了打击 而且会面对它
They've taken a beating, and they look it.
他们不是乌合之众
They're not a rabble.
他们像是军人在撤退
They're retreating like soldiers.
他们依然有战意
There's still fight in them.
我们要在哪叫他们 停下来战斗呢
Where are we gonna stop and put up the fight?
我们最后的一道防线 摩马士河
At our last line of defense, the River Meuse.
我们渡河在西岸筑工事
We'll cross it and dig in on the west bank.
至少我们会让德军弄湿
At least we'll get the Germans wet.
我拖你出安不列芙依然遗憾
Still sore I pulled you out of Ambleve?
我在那确认战事的结果，长官
I was contributing to the war effort there, sir.
在我们想办法阻挡他们时 试着别冻僵了你的脚
Try to keep your feet from freezing while we figure a way to stop them.
他们以前也犯过错
They've made mistakes before.
这一次他们会在那里犯错
Where have they made one this time?
他们让我生他们的气了
Well, they got me mad at them.
闭嘴，我们能走的
Shut up. We'll get there.
走呀，走呀
Come on. Come on.
继续走，继续走
Keep moving! Keep moving!
- 是什么留住你了  - 我没油了
- What's holding you up?  - I'm out of gas.
一小时前申请油料了 燃料车在什么地方
I reported low about an hour ago. Where's the fuel truck?
离开道路去等它 继续走
Get off the road and wait for it. Keep moving.
- 开到旁边去  - 开走
- Pull it over.  - Move it!
走呀
Come on!
继续走…
Keep moving.
继续走
Keep moving. Move it.
你要去哪？ 等一下行吗？
Where are you going? Will you wait a minute?
我需要汽油
I need gas.
这死王八蛋
Oh, get down.
你这个丑陋的混蛋
Why, you ugly jerk!
拿去，用你的大嘴巴用它吧
Here, use your big mouth on that.
来吧，我们去拿油吧
Hey, come on, let's get with it.
你们在笑什么？ 快来搬这玩意
What are you laughing at? Come and move this thing.
- 怎么啦？ 上士  - 搬起来
- You're all wet, sarge.  - Now get it up.
- 上士，你要这个干什么  - 你要这个干什么
- What are you gonna do with this?  - "What are you gonna do with this?"
虹吸原理，白痴，把它插进去
Siphon with it, idiot. Put it in.
- 你在想什么  - 和你想的一样
- What are you thinking?  - Same thing you are.
你抓回来的那些战俘 我们在他们身上找到橡皮管
Those prisoners you brought had rubber hoses on them.
他们带那个是在吸汽油吗？
They've been carrying those to siphon gas?
在瓦尔河时我看到 燃料车的油桶
At the Our River, I saw a German fuel truck...
掉进河里，它们飘在水面
...drop oil drums in the water, they floated.
- 你们两在说些什么  - 汽油，长官
- What the hell are you talking about?  - Gasoline, sir.
空的油桶及士兵带着橡皮管 指出了一件事
Empty fuel drums and men carrying siphon hoses add up to one thing.
德军的汽油不足 必须四处搜刮
The Germans are low on gas. They have to forage for it.
那就是他们的弱点
That's their weakness.
- 把这个发去总部  - 长官
- Get this off to headquarters.  - Sir.
A:虎型坦克的燃料消耗量？
A, what is the fuel consumption of a Tiger tank?
B:攻击发起线 到瓦尔河的确实距离
B, the exact distance from the Siegfried Line to the Meuse River.
C:德军汽油储存量 预估有多少
C, what is the estimate of fuel reserves in the German army?
- 就这些  - 是的，长官，立刻发
- That's it.  - Yes, sir, right away.
你笑什么？ 白痴
What are you laughing at, you idiot?
巴斯东的确实情况如何
What is the situation in Bastogne?
我军已彻底包围了美军
Our forces have completely encircled the Americans.
他们的情况毫无希望 他们除了投降没有第二条路
Their situation is hopeless. They have no recourse but to surrender.
看看是什么来了，少尉
Hey, look what's coming. Lieutenant!
停
Halt!
德军指挥官
The German commander wishes to communicate...
想与巴斯东的美军指挥官对话
...with the American commander of the encircled town of Bastogne.
他现在有点忙 你心里想些什么
He's a little busy right now. What's on your mind?
德军指挥官致巴斯东美军指挥官
"From the German commanding general to the commander of American troops fighting in Bastogne.
由于战争局面的改变
With the changing fortunes of war...
在巴斯东附近的美军
...the U.S.A. Forces in and around Bastogne...
已经完全被优势的德军机械化部队包围
...have become completely surrounded by superior German armored units.
唯一能拯救美军
The only possibility to spare the American troops...
被全歼灭的机会 是他们光荣的投降
...from total annihilation is their honorable surrender...
那才能防止对无助平民的屠杀
...which will also prevent the slaughter of helpless civilians."
你们有一个小时来做停战答覆
You have one hour of truce to reply.
蒙上他的眼睛
Blindfold him.
带他到指挥部去
Take him up to the command post.
请重覆
Repeat, please.
就这些？
Is that all?
长官，我收到巴斯东的回音
Sir, I have a message from Bastogne.
怎么说？
What is it?
我不明白
I don't understand it.
巴斯东美军指挥官 致德军指挥官
"From the American commander of Bastogne to the German commander.
坚果（疯子）
Nuts."
疯子
Nuts.
在那边
Hey, over there.
是位军官
Hey, it's an officer.
我们真高兴见过你
Boy, are we glad to see you.
- 我们已经12个小时没吃东西了  - 我们迷路了
- I haven't eaten in 12 hours.  - We got lost.
慢着，等一下
Hold it. Wait a minute.
你认为我们该投降吗？ 少尉
Do you think we should surrender, lieutenant?
投降？
Surrender?
不！
No.
放松，全部放松
Just stay loose, all of you. Stay loose.
现在把那手电筒给我
Now, give me that light.
好了，散开来，休息一会
All right, spread out. Get some rest.
天亮我们就开始行动
We'll get started when it's light.
葛雷将军
General Grey.
长官，这刚到
Sir, this just came in.
- 你往那去，你往那去  - 你们有任何人到过 安不列芙吗？
- Move along.  - Any of you guys been to Ambleve?
等一等，那家伙 等一下行吗？
Wait a minute. Will you wait a minute?
- 听我说 你们到过安不列芙吗？  - 别这样，葛菲 我们会惹上麻烦
- Any of you guys been to Ambleve?  - Come on, Guffy, we'll get in trouble.
不，我必须知道
I gotta know.
我由安不列芙出来的
I've been to Ambleve.
- 你知道安蓓客栈？  - 是的
- You know Ambleve inn?  - Yeah.
它没事，对吧？
Well, it's okay, isn't it?
它片瓦不存
There's nothing left of it.
葛菲，别这样
Guffy, come on.
他们何时才要让我们作战？
When are they gonna let us fight?
我们走
Let's go.
这是你要求总部给的资料 长官
It's here, sir, the information you requested from headquarters.
没错
That's it.
他们没汽油了
They're running out of gas.
德军攻击的前锋现在在那里？
Where's the spearhead of the German advance right now?
我们收到消息是 过安不列芙四哩处朝西前进
We place it four miles past Ambleve, moving west.
你预测日出时他们会在那里？
Where will they be at daybreak?
若他们彻夜前进 他们该在油料库东方9哩处
If they travel all night, they should be nine miles due east of the fuel depot.
我们会在那等他们
We'll be there to meet them.
我要指挥我的坦克
I'm committing my tanks.
我们用F计划
We'll use plan F.
- 替我呼叫蓝码301  - 301
- Get me Blue Code 301.  - 301.
好了，上车 出发！出发！
All right, mount up. Crank them up. Let's go. Let's go.
出发！发动它们！发动它们
Let's go. Crank them up, crank them up.
看看那雾
Look at that fog.
它若不散我们就不会找到他们 我们就不会战斗
If it stays, we won't find them and we won't fight.
它若转晴了，他们会找到我们
If it lifts, they'll find us.
那会是我们的人及坦克的终结
And that will be the end of our men and our tanks.
而我在祈祷它睛天
And I'm praying that it lifts.
那会让我是什么样的人？
What does that make me, Dan?
一位将军
A general.
是那样吗？ 将军
Is that so, general?
非常的有趣
It's very interesting.
谢谢你，将军
Thank you, general.
我们的旅目前是前进的最远的
Our column has made the farthest advance.
我们的战车是前进最远的 是全德国所嘱目的
We have outrun the other panzers. The eyes of Germany are on us.
元首本人会为我授勋
The Führer himself will decorate me.
我们做到了，康拉德 我们做到了
We have done it, Conrad. We have done it.
那么我错了，我们赢了这战争
Then I was wrong. We have won the war.
没有
No.
你是说我们输了？
You mean we have lost?
没有
No.
我不了解 若我们没有赢我们又没有输
I don't understand. If we have not won and we have not lost...
那么是怎么回事？
...then what's happening?
可能发生最好的事 是战争会持续
The best thing possible is happening. The war will go on.
- 持续多久？  - 永远
- For how long?  - Indefinitely.
一直持续下去！
On and on and on.
- 但它必须要终结的  - 你是个傻瓜，康拉德
- But it must come to an end.  - You're a fool, Conrad.
我们在1941年就已晓得 我们永远赢不了的
Those of us who understood knew, in 1941, we could never win.
你是说，上校 我们打了三年
You mean, colonel, for three years, we have been fighting...
- 没有胜利希望的仗  - 胜利有许多种
- ...without any hope of victory?  - There are many kinds of victory.
德军是否能活下来 让我们还能穿着这身军服
For the German army to survive, for us to remain in uniform...
那就是我们的胜利
...that is our victory.
康拉德 世界毕竟不能除掉我们！
Conrad, the world is not going to get rid of us after all.
但，我们何时才能回家？
But when do we go home?
这就是我们的家
This is our home.
那我的儿子呢？ 我何时才能看到他们？ 他们会变成什么样子？
And my sons? When do I see them? What will become of them?
他们会变成德国军人 而你会以他们为傲
They will become German soldiers, and you will be proud of them.
康拉德
Conrad.
在安不列芙你给我吃的东西 还有吗？
You still have any of those delicacies left you offered me at Ambleve?
有，有的，长官
Yes, sir.
为我弄一下，我的胃口非常好
Prepare them for me, will you? I'm in very good appetite.
- 看到任何东西了吗？  - 什么也没有
- See anything?  - Nothing.
好像失踪了一样
It's like they disappeared.
- 发现他们了吗？  - 没有，长官
- They been spotted yet?  - No, sir.
他们一定利用晚上改变了方向
They must have changed course during the night.
再呼叫我们的侦察兵
Call our scouts again.
- 看到任何东西了吗？ 什么都没
- See anything?  - Nothing.
红河6号，红河6号
Red River Six. Red River Six.
侦察预定交战地区
Scouted designated territory.
没有德军坦克的踪影
No sign of German tanks.
视野20码都没有 他们不在这，否则我会听见的
Can't see 20 yards. They're nowhere around, or I'd hear something.
讲点道理，中校
Let's be reasonable, colonel.
这种雾没有任何东西会起飞 你怎么能期待我带你上去
You expect me to take you up? Nothing's flying in this fog.
那让你安全，乔 不会撞到别的飞机
That makes it safe. We won't bump into another plane.
那我们怎么能看到坦克群 我们的能见度是零
How can we see the panzer column when we have zero visibility?
你若不停止争论 我们都会得肺炎 坐到那操纵杆后面去
You'll catch pneumonia if you don't stop arguing. Get behind that stick.
且慢
Wait a minute.
飞行命令在那？
Where are the flying orders?
我要看它
I wanna see them.
我要知道是那个疯子批准的
I wanna know what lunatic issued them.
没有命令，乔，那疯子是我
There are no orders, Joe. I'm the lunatic.
我家庭中没有疯子
Well, there's no insanity in my family.
乔，我们不找到那坦克群 那就不会有坦克会战
If we don't find that panzer column, there will be no tank battle.
那我们得用步兵去阻止他们
We'll have to stop them with infantry.
很多人得战死 就因为你要保持安全距离
A lot of guys are gonna die to keep you safe and cozy.
你真的很会打重要害，中校 那太脏了
You sure know how to hit below the belt. That's dirty.
我们不是在打枕头仗，乔 抱歉它让你痛心
We're not in a pillow fight, Joe. Sorry it hurts.
上去吧！
Get in.
所有的报告都是没有，长官
All reports negative, sir.
他们一定在某个地方
Well, they must be someplace.
大地不可能就那样 吞灭了他们
The earth couldn't have just swallowed them up.
- 派出侦察巡逻队  - 是的，长官
- Send out additional patrols.  - Yes, sir.
我在这干什么？ 这就像是在灯泡中飞行一样
What am I doing up here? It's like flying inside a light bulb.
只要保持我给你的航向 我们会找到他们的
Just stay on the course I gave you. We'll find them.
- 你怎么知道  - 海斯勒在找汽油
- How do you know?  - Hessler's looking for gas.
他在以寻获我方的补给打赌 飞低一点
He's gambling on capturing our supply. Get lower.
- 我们已经在五百尺以下了  - 我们须找个陆标
- We're down to 500 feet.  - We just have to pick up a landmark.
这里到处都是山，中校 我们找个陆标就要撞上去了
Hills are all around. We'll pick up a landmark right in the kisser.
试着飞低一点
Try it a little lower.
- 我什么都看不见  - 好了，关掉发动机
- I can't see a damn thing.  - All right, cut your engine.
滑行并且听 我们不必看见他们 我们能听见他们
Glide and listen. We can hear them.
- 你是在告诉我 在两百尺上空滑行  - 别说话了，关掉发动机
- Are you telling me to glide at 200 feet?  - Cut the talk and the engine.
- 取消吧！  - 当然，现在我们再试一次
- I'm calling this off.  - Sure. Now, let's try it again.
好了，关掉发动机
Okay, cut your engine.
我们若只有一百尺高 我跳机把你留在这
If we were 100 feet higher, I'd jump and leave you here.
安静
Quiet.
那是油料库
There's the depot.
河在那里
There's the river.
德国人一定在南方
The column has to be due south.
那是你的航向
That's your course.
飞低到我们能看见的高度，乔
Get her down, Joe, where we can see.
- 我们的高度是多少  - 四百尺
- What's our altitude?  - Four hundred feet.
好了，关掉发动机
All right, cut the engine.
你听见了吗？
Do you hear that?
有，我们飞下去看看
Yeah. We're going down for a look.
点燃发动机，我们快离开这
Hit your engine, let's get out of here.
红河6号，红河6号 这里是红河2号 发现敌军战车旅
Red River Six, this is Red River Two. The enemy column sighted.
目前座标是873一144
Present position, map coordinates: 8-7-3, 1-4-4.
发现敌军战车旅，长官
Enemy column sighted, sir.
找到他们了
Found them.
座标位置是873一144
Present position, map coordinates: 8-7-3, 1-4-4.
重复，目视敌军战车旅
Repeat. Enemy column sighted.
请讲话，红河2号 请讲话，红河2号
Come in, Red River Two. Come in, Red River Two.
请讲话，红河2号
Come in, Red River Two.
- 通讯中断，长官  - 那座标是在那？
- Contact broken.  - Where's that coordinate?
- 就在这，长官  - 是什么地形？
- Right here.  - What's the terrain?
低丘陵地
Low rolling hills.
命令我们的坦克在那一点出战
Order our tanks to intercept them at that point.
- 是的，长官  - 红河2号
- Yes, sir.  - Red River Two.
- 那是凯利  - 我晓得
- That's Kiley.  - I know.
上面有架飞机！
There's a plane up there.
它有麻烦了
He's in trouble.
医护兵 医护兵
Medic! Medic!
施奈德
Schneider.
由史必兹堡来的气象报告
From Spitzbergen, the weather forecast.
暖气流要来了
Warm front moving in.
通知各战车旅，天气要转好了
Notify all columns, weather clearing.
敌军据报度过了摩马士河
Enemy forces are reported crossing the River Meuse.
派侦察兵去！ 我要知道数量及装备
Send scouts forward. I want their numbers and composition.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
康拉德，我的望远镜
Conrad. My binoculars.
康拉德
Conrad?
我跟你说了我的…
I was saying I wanted...
怎么回事？ 康拉德
What is it, Conrad?
没什么，长官
Nothing, sir.
我在说我要我的望远镜
I was saying I wanted my binoculars.
有什么不对了？
What's wrong?
我…想调去服别的勤务，长官
I would like to be transferred to other duties, sir.
- 你是怎么回事？  - 别问我，长官，调我去就是了
- What is the matter with you?  - Don't ask me, sir. Just transfer me.
- 作战勤务？  - 是的，长官
- For combat duty?  - Yes, sir.
你想作战？ 那很值得鼓励 但是为了什么？
You want to fight? Very admirable, but why?
私人原因，长官
Personal reasons, sir.
私人原因
Personal reasons.
私人原因，你想说些什么？
Personal reasons? What the devil are you trying to say?
德国士兵有权向他的指挥官
It's the right of every German soldier to ask permission...
申请调服其他勤务
...for a transfer to other duties.
指挥官有权知道请调原因
It is the right of every commanding officer to know the reason...
- 而我要听实话  - 实话？
- ...for the transfer, and I want the truth.  - The truth...
我是个傻瓜，我相信你
...is that I'm a fool. I believed in you.
但你是否相信这场战争
But all you believe in is the war.
你有了战争，你喜欢战争
You have the war. You like the war.
而我所有的只是我的儿子 而我不想失去他们
And all I have are my sons, and I don't want to lose them.
- 我对你的孩子没有责任  - 你有，你会让他们变成军人
- I'm not responsible for your children.  - You are. You'd make them soldiers.
- 是的，而且他们会战斗  - 而他们会死
- Yes. They will fight.  - They will die.
- 若有这个必要  - 为谁有必要？ 为了你？
- If necessary.  - Necessary for who? For you?
你不但是个傻瓜，你是个叛徒
You are not only a fool, you are a traitor.
而你是个杀人凶手
And you are a murderer.
你会谋杀我的儿子 你会谋杀我的国家
You would murder my sons. You would murder my country.
你会为了 继续穿那军服谋杀世界
You would murder the whole world to stay in that uniform.
只因为缅怀你是位朋友
It is only the memory of you as a friend...
使你免受军法审判，出去
...that prevents me from having you court-martialed. Get out.
我们的侦察兵看到有中型坦克
Our scouts have sighted a brigade of medium tanks.
- 在这种时刻？ 有炮兵吗？  - 没有
- Light armor at this point? Any artillery?  - None.
- 而且没有步兵  - 他们在投入预备队
- And no infantry.  - They're committing their reserves.
我们摧毁了它们 在油料库与我们之间就没东西了
We destroy them, they have nothing between us and the fuel depot.
- 把所有的步兵都调到后面去  - 是的，长官
- Send all infantry to the rear.  - Yes, sir.
迪波 派这个人到燃料车去
Diepel, assign this man to fuel trucks.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
长官，敌军朝我们阵地前进
Sir, enemy advancing on our position.
很好 他们在吃饵了
Good. They've taken the bait.
比瑞奇！
Pritchard...
我们要测试总部 给我们的资料了
...we're going to test that information we got from headquarters.
若是正确的
If it's accurate...
我们就让他们没汽油了
...we'll run them out of gas.
老虎呼叫各部队 盖顶盖！前进
Tiger to all units, close hatches. Forward.
屠夫营，将坦克转向侧翼
Butcher, swing up and take positions on the ridges.
小心那山坡 没时间损失在路上
And watch that damn gully. This is no time to lose a track.
他们来了
Here they come.
别射击，等他们全进入射程
Hold your fire till they're right on us.
用穿甲弹，每一发都要命中
Load with hypershot. Make every one count.
- 别射击  - 要等多久
- Hold your fire.  - How long?
直到我叫你射
Until I tell you!
我们以重叠队形进攻
Attack in staggered formation.
狮营在第一线，豹营在第二线
First, Lion on the assault. Second, Panther.
记住 在有效射程内再开始射击
Remember, hold your fire till they're within effective range.
- 我们要等多久？  - 直到我们能打中腹部
- How long are we gonna wait?  - Until we can hit a soft spot.
稳住
Steady.
别射击，别射击
Hold it. Hold it.
让他们开进来，让他们进来
Let them come on in. Let them come in. That's the way.
就是那样！现在！ 让他们尝尝！
Now! Let them have it!
再射击一发就离开这山脊
Fire one more round, then let's get the hell off this ridge.
有一辆由右边来了 看见了吗？
There's one coming up over the rise. You see him?
别紧张，孩子们，预备！
Steady, boy. Ready on.
射击！
Fire!
老虎呼叫豹营，向左分散 老虎呼叫狮营，向右分散
Tiger to Panther, spread out to left. Lion, spread out to right.
我们试着包围它们
We will try to encircle.
谢曼型受伤了，把它们全干掉
Sherman damaged. We'll finish it off.
射击 命中！
Fire! It's a hit.
下一辆，11点方向900
The next, 11 o'clock, 900.
迎上去，和他们混在起
Get in among them.
让他们不能射击免得彼此互射
Mix with them so they can't fire without hitting each other.
屠夫一号，这里是屠夫3号 有辆德军战车在一点钟方向
Butcher One, this is Butcher Three. There's a Kraut at 1 o'clock...
在它天线上有面三角旗
...with a pennant on his antenna.
这一辆属于我，它是我的
This one belongs to me. He's mine.
它在那了
There he is.
向左转，左边 现在向右转半圈，右转半圈
All right, kick her left, kid. Left. Now, hard right! Hard right!
着它，射程900 向上两格
Stay with them! Range, 9-0-0. Up two.
射击！
Fire!
射的漂亮，我们打中他了
Good shot! We got him!
再装填，没发生任何事
Load again. Nothing has happened.
留神，他们看到我们了 快点！我们离开这里
Hey, watch it. They see us. Hey, let's get out of here.
瞄准他逃跑路线的前缘
Aim just ahead as he runs.
射击！
Fire!
屠夫1号，这里是屠夫3号
Butcher One, this is Butcher Three.
请回答 请讲，屠夫3号 损害报告，请回答
Come in, Butcher Three. Report damage. Over.
有一名阵亡两名负伤 但我们依然能打！
I've got one dead and two wounded, but we can still fight.
你的炮没了，撤离 试着开回重整区，请回答
You lost your gun. Pull out. Try to make it back to the assembly area.
我们不需要炮，我们能撞它！
We don't need a gun! We can ram them.
葛菲，你的车毁了
Guffy, you're all busted up.
离开那回重整区去 那是命令！ 通话完毕
Get out of there and make it back to the assembly area. That's an order. Out.
开到山丘上去
Get her over the hill.
好好的开
Driver, halt.
我们试着全收拾掉
Let's try to pick them off.
十点钟方向，距离8百 射击！
Ten o'clock. Sherman, 800. Fire!
贝克营报告，两辆全毁
Baker Battalion reporting in.
一辆受损不能作战
Two tanks destroyed, one damaged, out of action.
幽灵营报告，六辆全毁 九辆不能作战
Phantom Battalion reports six tanks destroyed, nine out of action.
屠夫营报告，11辆坦克全毁 8辆在起火
Butcher Battalion reports 11 tanks destroyed, eight on fire.
继续消耗他们的汽油
Keep burning up their gas.
老虎呼叫基地，我回来加油了
Commander to base, I am returning to refuel.
我们把他们打的粉碎
We are cutting them to pieces.
而他们在让我们的坦克没油
And they are emptying our tanks.
他们在故意牺牲他们的战车 好消耗我们的汽油
They are deliberately sacrificing their armor to bleed us dry.
- 离油料库还有多远？  - 12公里
- What is the distance to the fuel depot?  - Twelve kilometers.
你继续这里的战役
You will continue the battle here.
让他们相信他们的战术成功了
Let them believe their strategy is succeeding.
我要15辆坦克以及所有的空卡车
I want 15 tanks and all the empty trucks.
- 我要去油料库了  - 是的，15辆坦克及空卡车
- I'm going on to the depot.  - Yes, sir, 15 tanks and fuel trucks.
出发
Forward.
来吧！士兵，你办得到的
Hey, come on, soldier. You can make it.
开到路边去
Pull it off the road!
- Wait!  - Come on! Come on!
开到路边去，开过去
Pull it off the road! Pull it off!
别碰坦克
Get off the tank.
- 离坦克远一点  - 你有足够的空间
- Stay off the tank!  - You've got plenty of room.
- 能带这些人  - 这辆坦克那都不去
- You can carry these guys.  - This tank ain't going no place.
别上坦克
Get off the tank!
不论你要去那，最好是用走的
Wherever you're going, you better walk.
- 你在这等什么？  - 我在等德国人
- What are you waiting here for?  - For the Germans.
他们得经过这里
They gotta come by here.
我还有挺机枪
And I still got a machine gun.
用那个起不了什么作用
There's not much you can do with that.
- 你还剩下多少弹药？  - 两弹带
- How much ammo do you have left?  - Two belts.
那可以解决一些他们
That will take care of some of them.
你那有个负伤的 你该找医护兵了
You got a wounded man. You think you ought to get him to the medics?
他不算太重，还能继续打
Oh, he's not too bad. He can still fight.
上车，各位
Get on, fellas.
把这辆坦克调头向西 开去马士尔河的
Pull this tank back. Head it west towards the River Meuse.
我警告你，少尉 离我的坦克远一点
I'm warning you, lieutenant, stay off my tank.
不是放下那把枪就是开火 上士
Either put up that gun or fire it, sergeant.
没事的，上士，没事的
It's okay, sarge. It's okay.
将军！另一队坦克
General, another panzer column has been spotted four miles...
- 在马士尔河4哩外被发现  - 它们由哪来的？
- ...from the River Meuse.  - Where did they come from?
给我接负责油料库的军官
Get me the officer in charge of the fuel depot.
那是201，快点
Get Silver Cloud 201. Quickly.
那不是新的队伍
It's not a new column.
是海斯勒
It's Hessler.
- 由战场上溜走！  - 油料库，长官
- He slipped away from the battle.  - The fuel depot, sir.
我是葛雷将军 我亲自给你这个命令
General Grey speaking. I'm giving you this order personally.
立刻毁掉油料库
Destroy the fuel depot at once. I repeat.
我再说一次 立刻毁掉油料库！
Destroy the fuel depot at once.
是的，长官 我立刻毁了油料库，长官 烧了他！
Yes, sir. I'll destroy the depot immediately, sir. Set it on fire.
是的，长官，一滴不剩 我会确定的，长官 一滴也没有
No, sir, not a drop. I'll make sure of that, sir. They won't get a drop.
我们把这些尸体弄离开这！快
All right, let's get these bodies out of here. Let's go. Move!
各部队都回报缺乏燃料，长官
Elke and Eisner report fuel exhausted, sir.
海斯勒目前的位置在那里？
What's Hessler's present position?
他报告离美军油料库 还有3公里
He reports being three kilometers from the American fuel depot.
我们一定要到达那里
We must get there.
他会办到的！ 海斯勒会办到的
He will do it. Hessler will do it.
不要开枪，我来用说的
No shooting. I'll do the talking.
回你的岗位去
Get back to your post.
- 停在那，上士  - 停车！
- Hold it up there, sergeant.  - Stop it.
- 停车！有何效劳之处？  - 我们没油了，你能加满吗？
- What can I do for you boys?  - We just made it. Could you fill her up?
当然，帮我一下，士兵，当然
Sure. Give you a hand, soldier. Sure.
下士，弄几桶油过来
Corporal, bring some of those cans over here.
你们帮帮忙，行吗？
A couple of you boys help out.
上士，我们会帮你加满油 你马上就能上路了
Sergeant, we'll have you gassed up and on your way in no time.
去拿你的机枪
Get on your machine gun.
- 少尉  - 嗯？
- Hey, lieutenant.  - Yeah?
你在瓦尔河指挥交通吗？
Weren't you directing traffic at the Our River Bridge?
安不列芙的路标 还指向美乐地吗？
Does the road to Ambleve still lead to Malmedy?
停车！
Stop.
这个油料库一定要被俘获
This fuel dump must be taken intact.
不准射击
No shooting.
- 看！我们离开这！  - 站住！站住！想来劫油的，
- Look. Let's get out of here.  - Hold it. They'll capture the gas.
不能就这样不管
We can't just leave it.
- 你还在等什么？ 少尉，我们走  - 站住，他们要我们的汽油
- What are you waiting for? Let's go.  - Hold it! They're after the gas.
- 我们得把它炸掉  - 我们不能对那一堆丢火柴呀！
- We ought to blow it up.  - We can't set a match to all that.
- 我们没接到命令，少尉  - 我在下令！
- We got no orders, lieutenant.  - Yeah? Well, I'm giving the orders.
少尉，其中之一还活着
Hey, lieutenant, one of them is still alive.
别射，别射，是我们的人
Hold it! Hold it! He's one of ours.
- 我扶住你了，中校  - 放火！
- I got you, colonel.  - Burn it.
- 别紧张 长官，我知道该怎么做  - 放火！
- Take it easy. I know what to do.  - Burn it.
- 好吧 过来扶他一把！  - 放火！
- Give him a hand, if you can.  - Burn it.
来呀！你们还在等什么？ 来呀
Come on, I'm waiting for you! Come on!
把那一端的油桶推倒 别开枪，葛菲
Get those barrels off the end of that ramp. Hold your fire, Guffy.
把你的坦克开到那堆油桶后面 直到我叫你推
Move your tank behind that pile until I tell you to shove.
你拿个手榴弹给我！ 快点！
You, get me some hand grenades off the tank. Come on.
快点！快点！
Come on.
你！到那油罐车去 把所有的开关都打开
You, get to that gas truck and open all the valves.
而且离它远一点！
Then get the hell away from it.
好了，把它们滚下去！
All right, roll them down.
离开路面
Get off the road.
给我颗手榴弹！
Give me a hand grenade.
他要逃了
He's getting away.
好，推！
Okay, shove.
别停！继续走！别停！
Don't stop! Keep going! Don't stop!
把这个报回总部
Get this message to headquarters:
他们遗弃了 他们的坦克走回德国
They've abandoned their tanks, and they're walking back to Germany.
本片是献给 在第二次世界大战中
参加过本伟大战役的一百万人
为了表现所有参与者，地名，名字和个性的对本次胜利的贡献
本片进行综合
以体现本次战役的精神与精华
剧终